{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Cramp", "Diaphoresis", "Anhedonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Tachypnea", "Opisthotonus", "Thrombocytopenia", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Genital ulcer", "Dysmenorrhea", "Thought insertion", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Hypertriglyceridemia", "Delirium", "Headache", "Torticollis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Apnea", "Sundowning", "Hallucination", "Xerostomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Tachycardia", "Dysarthria", "Hypomimia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Psoas sign", "Chills", "Anhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Coma", "Swollen testicle", "Mood swing", "Tinnitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heat Stroke?", "answers": ["Flushing", "Iritis", "Vaginal odor", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Pretibial myxedema", "Mouth ulcer", "Eye discharge", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Self-destructive behaviour", "Vaginitis", "Bleeding gums", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Pain", "Metabolic acidosis", "Tendonitis", "Nikolsky's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Lymphocytosis", "Skin rash", "Polyphagia", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Stunted growth", "Chronic cough", "Microalbuminuria", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Dieting", "Night Sweats", "Lethargy", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Hematemesis", "Azotemia", "Diabetes mellitus", "Tetany"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Asymptomatic", "Kaposi's sarcoma", "Hemoptysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Loose teeth", "Diabetes mellitus", "Heartburn", "Hyperlipidemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Pelvic pain", "Alopecia", "Acanthosis nigricans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Ataxia", "Mental illness", "Cyst", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Clouding of consciousness", "Vision disorder", "Glossitis", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Metrorrhagia", "Rectal prolapse", "Blister", "Stiff neck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Nocturnal enuresis", "Risky behavior", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Synovitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Dacryoadenitis", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Tunnel vision", "Acne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Infertility", "Rectal tenesmus", "Lethargy", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Conjunctivitis", "Abdominal pain", "Itchy eyes", "Conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Hypoesthesia", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Facial Paresis", "Glabellar reflex", "Osteoporosis", "Visual verbal agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Lactose intolerance", "Joint effusion", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Poor wound healing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Steatorrhea", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Xeroderma", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Low-grade fever", "Vital Exhaustion", "Sore throat", "Indigestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Hiccup", "Post-nasal drip", "Intertrigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Bubo", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Short stature", "Bronchophony"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Sleep disorder", "Flatulence", "Intermittent claudication", "Cyst"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Myxedema", "Weight loss", "Chronic pain", "Social isolation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Leukopenia", "Bronchiectasis", "Bleeding gums", "Cramp"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Hyperglycemia", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Rumination", "Stereotypy", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Toe walking", "Orofacial pain", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Hyperlipidemia", "Biliary colic", "Pruritus", "Abscess"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Painless testicular lump", "Breakthrough bleeding", "Abdominal distension", "Toothache"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Akathisia", "Asymmetry", "Delayed puberty", "Ageusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Cerebellar ataxia", "Glossitis", "Nosebleed", "Skin tag"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Lymphocytosis", "Fibromyalgia", "Spinal tumor", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Muehrcke's nails", "Frequent urination", "Iron deficiency", "Trousseau sign of malignancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Anhedonia", "Nightmare", "Dysautonomia", "Bone Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Constipation", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Dandruff", "Leukorrhea", "Brittle nails", "Ageusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Loss of smell", "Rectal pain", "Hypertriglyceridemia", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Celiac disease?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Heberden's node", "Thought disorder", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Hemiparesis", "Thyroid nodule", "Headache", "Dyskinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Iritis", "Skin rash", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Painful ejaculation", "Fatigue", "Air crescent sign", "Impetigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Intrusive thoughts", "Anuria", "Vomiting", "Aphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Bradycardia", "Abdominal pain", "Nipple discharge", "Photophobia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Watery eyes", "Hyperkeratosis", "Cyanosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Male infertility", "Phonophobia", "Paranoia", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Rose spots", "Purpura", "Lipodystrophy", "Meningism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Stiffness", "Maculopapular rash", "Dysentery", "Loss of smell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Asterixis", "Nuchal Rigidity", "Apnea", "Myopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Short stature", "Joint effusion", "Pallor", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Delayed onset muscle soreness", "Facial Paresis", "Fever", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Gingivitis", "Tachycardia", "Caput medusae"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Nocturnal Cough", "Seizure", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Chills", "Rectal bleeding", "Bronchophony"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "Akathisia", "Oral candidiasis", "Inferiority complex"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Meningitis?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Thrombosis", "Uremia", "Proteinuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Leukoplakia", "Nightmare", "Nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Delirium", "Paget's disease of the breast"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Dry cough", "Sleep deprivation", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Bell's palsy", "Knee pain", "Bleeding diathesis", "Torticollis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Failure to thrive", "Fatigue", "Labored breathing", "Acute bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Anal discharge", "Enophthalmia", "Tenderness", "Left ventricular hypertrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Myopathy", "Dermatosis", "Chronic pain", "Racing thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Homicidal ideation", "Myelopathy", "Pruritus ani", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Leg pain", "Swelling", "Depression", "Orthostatic hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Delusion", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Pruritus", "Hypercapnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Tophus", "Mouth ulcer", "Gastric varices"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gout?", "answers": ["Hypomimia", "Body ache", "Joint pain", "Vision loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Bronchospasm", "Toothache", "Hyperkeratosis", "Rebound tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Short stature", "Anhidrosis", "Diplopia", "Xeroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Lack of Remorse", "Hallucination", "Skin rash", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Abdominal distension", "Pain", "Vesical tenesmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Nystagmus", "Nikolsky's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Hematospermia", "Thrombosis", "Polyneuropathy", "Blister"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Heartburn", "Vaginal odor", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Cracked Skin", "Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Desquamation", "Stunted growth", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Brittle nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Middle back pain", "Angina Pectoris", "Avolition", "Flushing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Dehydration", "Paraphasia", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Stiff neck", "Dyschezia", "Erythema", "Retrograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tinea pedis?", "answers": ["Medulloblastoma", "Purpura", "Scaly skin", "Foul smelling urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Xerostomia", "Urinary incontinence", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Sleep deprivation", "Encephalopathy", "Dacryoadenitis", "Urinary Frequency"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Acanthosis nigricans", "Dermatosis", "Fecal incontinence", "Sensorineural hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Pathological laughing and crying", "Diarrhea", "Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Erectile dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Bone fracture", "Scaly skin", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Hearing problem", "Facial pain", "Frequent urination"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Fetor hepaticus", "Hematemesis", "Torticollis", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Loss of smell", "Malaise", "Painful ejaculation", "Dysautonomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Paralysis", "Flaccid paralysis", "Delayed puberty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Cold sensitivity", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Heart murmur", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Tic", "Hutchinson's sign", "Bone pain", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Paresthesia", "Hematuria", "Irregular menstruation", "Acalculia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Pathological laughing and crying", "Pressure of speech", "Urinary retention", "Speech disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prostate cancer?", "answers": ["Dysuria", "Orthopnea", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Coma", "Oliguria", "Abdominal pain", "Hallucination"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Pale feces", "Panic attack", "Stunted growth", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Angina Pectoris", "Coagulopathy", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Hormonal disorders", "Nausea", "Guilt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Necrosis", "Myocardial infarction", "Biliary colic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Emaciation", "Vaginal dryness", "Fever", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gallstone?", "answers": ["Vomiting", "Hyperlipidemia", "Pancreatitis", "Nervousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Cullen's sign", "Hypoglycemia", "Rose spots", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Stomatitis", "Pulmonary edema", "Hypertriglyceridemia", "Extreme Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Abscess", "Delayed reading ability", "Pectus carinatum", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Post-nasal drip", "Pancolitis", "Microalbuminuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Excessive Crying", "Obturator sign", "Hypercholesterolemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Ventricular tachycardia", "Peripheral neuropathy", "cerebella tumor", "Hiccup"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Dyskinesia", "Hyperglycemia", "Mouth ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Polyuria", "Eye discharge", "Glabellar reflex"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Hyperpigmentation", "Waxy flexibility", "Hyperlipidemia", "Deformity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Ecchymosis", "Stunted growth", "Polyphagia", "Tic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Fatty liver", "Snoring", "Avolition", "Ascites"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Hyperhidrosis", "Dissociative disorder", "Abdominal obesity", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Pericarditis", "Bone tumor", "Albuminuria", "Arthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Difficulty Focusing", "Infection", "Delayed puberty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Vision disorder", "Scaly skin", "Quadriplegia", "Poor wound healing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Tenderness", "Hypersexuality", "Glycosuria", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Polydipsia", "Vesical tenesmus", "Urethritis", "Urinary incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Intestinal varices", "Proteinuria", "Rumination", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Malocclusion", "Rhonchi", "Fatigue", "Photosensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Anger", "Dementia", "Erectile dysfunction", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Vaginal tenderness", "Weight loss", "Dissociative disorder", "Bronchospasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 2 diabetes?", "answers": ["Hyperaemia", "Dermatitis", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Cracked Skin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Golden S sign", "Conjunctivitis", "Shivering"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Malaise", "Lipodystrophy", "Hyperaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Gingival enlargement", "Lack of Remorse", "Polyuria", "Hyperglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Blister", "Urethritis", "Eczema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Urge incontinence", "Restricted behavior", "Delayed puberty", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Hematochezia", "Stupor", "Nausea", "Flashback"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Internal bleeding", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Post-void dribbling", "Air crescent sign", "Lipodystrophy", "Biliary colic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Hematospermia", "Chronic cough", "Hives"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Medulloblastoma", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Chemosis", "Lumbago", "Hyperesthesia", "Eye pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Bleeding gums", "Diarrhea", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Polydipsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Abdominal obesity", "Dissociative disorder", "Hematuria", "Melanocytic nevus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Cracked Skin", "Hypersomnia", "Polyphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Failure to thrive", "Breakthrough bleeding", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Odynophagia", "Hematochezia", "Hyperkalemia", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Urinary incontinence", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Steatorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Microalbuminuria", "Parosmia", "Narcissism", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Bronchophony", "Alopecia", "Headache", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Painless testicular lump", "Gastric varices", "Bone tumor", "Pyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Hypertriglyceridemia", "Vomiting", "Verbosity", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Fetor hepaticus", "Splenomegaly", "Nocturnal enuresis", "Rectal prolapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Eosinophilia", "Sputum", "Back pain", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Hypoglycemia", "Frequent urination", "Bloating", "Anasarca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Wheeze", "Hypoesthesia", "Acute bronchitis", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Anhedonia", "Dysuria", "Sundowning", "Meningism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Bleeding on probing", "Melena", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Ventricular tachycardia", "Urinary retention", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca", "Morphea", "Silhouette sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Eczema", "Foul smelling urine", "Vision disorder", "Gait abnormality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Blumberg sign", "Muscle Spasms", "Sleep disturbances", "Neuralgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Urinary tract infection", "Horner's syndrome", "Tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Dystonia", "Vaginal bleeding", "Rectal pain", "Rectal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Vision loss", "Dysphoria", "Persistent urge to urinate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Raynaud's phenomenon", "Fever", "Feeling of impending doom", "Leukopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Urinary Frequency", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Erythema nodosum", "Dyspareunia", "Dystonia", "Loss of smell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Cramp", "Mole color changes", "Renal colic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Terry's nails", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Urinary urgency", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Blood in stool", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Lethargy", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Testicle pain", "Enthesitis", "Vesical tenesmus", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Asthma", "Brittle nails", "Asymptomatic", "Orthostatic hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Barrel chest", "Chills", "Male infertility", "Rumination"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Urinary tract infection?", "answers": ["Stereotypy", "Wart", "Pain", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aneurysm?", "answers": ["Myoclonus", "Pneumonia", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aneurysm?", "answers": ["Apnea", "Sore throat", "Radiculopathy", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aneurysm?", "answers": ["Xerophthalmia", "Testicle pain", "Bleeding", "Swollen tonsils"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aneurysm?", "answers": ["Tachypnea", "Dysphonia", "Grandiose delusion", "Azotemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aneurysm?", "answers": ["Phonological deficit", "Dysphagia", "Hypersomnia", "Hepatomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Meningism", "Weight gain", "Deformity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Eosinophilia", "Delayed reading ability", "Coma", "Sinusitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Spider angioma", "Convulsion", "Feeling of impending doom", "Mouth breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Self-harm", "Proteinuria", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Personality or behavior changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Floater", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Lumbago", "Paresthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Immunodeficiency", "Hyperglycemia", "Clouding of consciousness", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Phyllodes tumor", "Bone tumor", "Abdominal pain", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Blurred vision", "Urge incontinence", "Cold sensitivity", "Irregular menstruation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Astasia-abasia", "Dieting", "Sputum", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Oliguria", "Psychomotor retardation", "Aphasia", "Dysgeusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Stridor", "Anal swelling", "Fatigue", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Upper respiratory tract infection", "Water retention", "Drooling", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Headache", "Apnea", "Weight loss", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Hepatorenal syndrome", "Apathy", "Vasoconstriction", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Hepatomegaly", "Alopecia", "Jaundice", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Burning Chest Pain", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Abnormal vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Orthostatic hypotension", "Swollen legs", "Cervicitis", "Biliary colic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Erythema nodosum", "Catatonia", "Hypersalivation", "Swollen feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Malnutrition", "Facial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Clonus", "Seborrheic dermatitis", "Urinary Frequency", "Kaposi's sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Shock", "Dizziness", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Body ache", "Edema", "Ventricular tachycardia", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Hyperreflexia", "Hematoma", "Self-harm", "Erythema nodosum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Hypotension", "Rheumatoid nodule", "Hyperkalemia", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Bruxism", "Melanocytic nevus", "Coagulopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pre-eclampsia?", "answers": ["Vomiting", "Hyperkalemia", "Spasmodic dysphonia", "Hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Dysphoria", "Impulsivity", "Horner's syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Psoas sign", "Malaise", "Hypersalivation", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Hepatorenal syndrome", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Nail clubbing", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Caput medusae", "Hyperphosphatemia", "Polyneuropathy", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Hyperactivity", "Clonus", "Nikolsky's sign", "Dysuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Swollen tonsils", "Conjunctivitis", "Impulsivity", "Hypervigilance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Polydipsia", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Restless legs syndrome", "Trismus", "Fibromyalgia", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Knee pain", "Anhedonia", "Watery diarrhea", "Granuloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Swollen lymph nodes", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Blumberg sign", "Globus pharyngis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Vaginal tenderness", "Aphasia", "Hunger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Feeling of impending doom", "Carelessness", "Fatigue", "Emotional insecurity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Pelvic pain", "Personality or behavior changes", "Anterograde amnesia", "Rovsing's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Alopecia", "Bone Loss", "Dry cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Genital wart", "Brittle nails", "Anal swelling", "Urinary retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Erectile dysfunction", "Gastric varices", "Lumbago", "Genital sores"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Hypomimia", "Inflammation", "Deformity", "Polydipsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Personality or behavior changes", "Impetigo", "Bell's palsy", "Paresthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Nocturnal Cough", "Swelling", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Dysarthria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Petechia", "Bleeding", "Aggression", "Numbness of face"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Slurred Speech", "Mole color changes", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Coma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Tic", "Skin ulcer", "Burning Chest Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Sensorineural hearing loss", "Border irregularity", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Nikolsky's sign", "Hallucination", "Proctitis", "Asterixis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Male infertility", "Erythema nodosum", "Nocturnal enuresis", "Insomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Blackout", "Pathological laughing and crying", "Skin rash", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Shock", "Feeling of impending doom", "Frequent urination", "Phyllodes tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Clonus", "Dysentery", "Mouth ulcer", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Headache", "Meningism", "Delirium"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Thought insertion", "Horner's syndrome", "Stomatitis", "Disregard for right and wrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Dysautonomia", "Cachexia", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Apnea", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Vision disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Major depression", "Erythema multiforme", "Hives", "Pulmonary hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Fecal incontinence", "Red eye", "Asthma", "Pruritus ani"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Bone Loss", "Hypocalcaemia", "Pain", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Blister", "Fasciculation", "Groin Lump", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Hypoesthesia", "Gingivitis", "Blackout", "Carpal tunnel syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Mouth breathing", "Clonus", "Chills", "Bleeding on probing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Dysgeusia", "Central facial palsy", "Maculopapular rash", "Anal fissure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Cyanosis", "Decreased level of consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Hemiparesis", "Erythema", "Hegar's sign", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Ascites", "Vision disorder", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Pus", "Hyperventilation", "Pica", "Sore throat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Floater", "Anasarca", "Stereotypy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Photopsia", "Narrow stools", "Genital ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Dysarthria", "Flashback", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Vaginal discharge", "Glabellar reflex", "Dysosmia", "Cervical lymphadenopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Dacryoadenitis", "Difficulty walking", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Pus", "Hypervigilance", "Tunnel vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Caput medusae", "Trismus", "Hypothermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes simplex?", "answers": ["Cotton wool spots", "Intellectual disability", "Formication", "Halitosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Giardiasis?", "answers": ["Dysautonomia", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Wheeze", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Steatorrhea", "Blackout", "Bradypnea", "Feeling of fullness in the ear"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Syncope", "Rectal tenesmus", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Cramp", "Anasarca", "Phonological deficit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Abdominal distension", "Facial nerve paralysis", "Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Cullen's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Stuttering", "Nail clubbing", "Desquamation", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Sinusitis", "Personality or behavior changes", "Ileus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Bone fracture", "Hypokinesia", "Tenderness", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Constipation", "Gingival recession", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Pulmonary hypertension", "Chorioretinitis", "Muscle Spasms", "Aphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Myoclonus", "Low-grade fever", "Hematochezia", "Pericarditis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Nausea", "Difficulty walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Vascular Leak", "Thought insertion", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Acute abdomen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Spasmodic dysphonia", "Dementia", "Male infertility", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Vital Exhaustion", "Pain", "Groin Lump", "Bigger mole diameter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Tumor", "Ageusia", "Opisthotonus", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Loss of interest", "Blood in stool", "Photosensitivity", "Purpura"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Swollen legs", "Uremia", "Flatulence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulosis?", "answers": ["Vesical tenesmus", "Asymptomatic", "Loss of smell", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Fatty liver", "Fever", "Audible pop at time of injury", "Hypertonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Dermatosis", "Anorexia", "Urinary incontinence", "Nipple tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Splenomegaly", "Erythema multiforme", "Watery diarrhea", "Nipple tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Rumination", "Loss of smell", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Hyperreflexia", "Sneeze", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Intertrigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Blumberg sign", "Diarrhea", "Pressure of speech", "Maculopapular rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Fibromyalgia", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Diplopia", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Vomiting", "Mania", "Water retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Eosinophilia", "Joint pain", "Pericarditis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Cullen's sign", "Balance disorder", "Ascites", "Verbosity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Cloudy urine", "Suicidal ideation", "Hyperesthesia", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Golden S sign", "Cirrhosis", "Urinary retention", "Polyphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Dysphonia", "Anal discharge", "Hepatomegaly", "Bruise"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Dyskinesia", "Cyst", "Hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Irregular menstruation", "Ageusia", "Abdominal pain", "Hot flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Headache", "Risus sardonicus", "Menorrhagia", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis?", "answers": ["Increased vaginal discharge", "Loss Of Consciousness", "Muscle pain", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Indigestion?", "answers": ["Grandiose delusion", "Hyperphosphatemia", "Heartburn", "Catatonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Indigestion?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Hepatomegaly", "Dyspareunia", "Delirium"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Indigestion?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Catatonia", "Bloating", "Diaphoresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Indigestion?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Spasticity", "Nausea", "Abnormal vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Indigestion?", "answers": ["Peripheral neuropathy", "Barrel chest", "Blackout", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Rectal pain", "Nipple tenderness", "Palpitation", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Infection", "Night terror", "Dysentery", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Agitation", "Pus", "Photosensitivity", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Collapse", "Coprolalia", "Brittle nails", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Headache", "Sadness", "Stomatitis", "Micrographia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Slurred Speech", "Polyneuropathy", "Metabolic acidosis", "Insomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Hyperhidrosis", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Impetigo", "Tinnitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Metabolic acidosis", "Fatty liver", "Diarrhea", "Enthesitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Generalized anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Stomatitis", "Cough", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Narcissistic personality disorder?", "answers": ["Gynecomastia", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Hypomania", "Paraphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Addison's disease?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Chorioretinitis", "Weight loss", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Gingivitis", "Muscle pain", "Diaphoresis", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Dysphagia", "Hutchinson's sign", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Phlebitis", "Hyperactivity", "Cold sensitivity", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Intellectual disability", "Psychomotor retardation", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Chancre", "Pyuria", "Spasticity", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Echolalia", "Trismus", "Phyllodes tumor", "Catatonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Opisthotonus", "Dry cough", "Otorrhea", "Shivering"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Hepatic encephalopathy", "Malaise", "Risus sardonicus", "Tonsillitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tetanus?", "answers": ["Pursed lip breathing", "Abdominal distension", "Markle sign", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Hemiparesis", "Fatigue", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Papule"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Crepitus", "Phyllodes tumor", "Mouth ulcer", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Bruxism", "Ataxia", "Xeroderma", "Bruise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Pectus carinatum", "Back pain", "Hyperaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Purpura", "Polyneuropathy", "Numbness", "Fourth heart sound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Ketoacidosis", "Diplopia", "Osteoporosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Maculopapular rash", "Edema", "Asthma", "Dysmenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Flaccid paralysis", "Headache", "Sadness", "Aggression"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Scleritis", "Coagulopathy", "Muscle pain", "Otalgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Hyperhidrosis", "Difficulty walking", "Thrombocytopenia", "Myopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Candidiasis", "Xerophthalmia", "Emaciation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "/m/0lxt", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Dissociative disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Dry cough", "Fibromyalgia", "Candidiasis", "Loss of interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Water retention", "Glossodynia", "Night terror", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Skin Discoloration", "Cyanosis", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Nipple discharge", "Anger", "Fever", "Hunger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Rovsing's sign", "Thrombosis", "Tremor", "Abdominal obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Paranoia", "Leukorrhea", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Auditory hallucination", "Leukorrhea", "Dyschezia", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Urinary incontinence", "Cyanosis", "Dysesthesia", "Dermatosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Watery diarrhea", "Stuttering", "Seizure", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Blister", "Dark urine", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Snoring", "Flashback", "Myerson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Dizziness", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Leukocytosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Hypersalivation", "Gingival recession", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Hypokinesia", "Sore throat", "Opportunistic infection", "Hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Nipple discharge", "Pain", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Cardiac asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Stroke", "Hirano body", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Conjunctivitis", "Abscess", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Dermatitis", "Akathisia", "Risky behavior", "Hyperphosphatemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Middle back pain", "Barrel chest", "Proteinuria", "Balance disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Urge incontinence", "Anhidrosis", "Infertility", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Iritis", "Photosensitivity", "Hepatosplenomegaly", "Slurred Speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Hypoglycemia", "Arthritis", "Hypoxia", "Tachypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Hyperglycemia", "Ataxia", "Floater", "Nephrotic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Impulsivity", "Hematuria", "Hypoxemia", "Dysautonomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Hypothermia", "Chemosis", "Leukopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Hearing problem", "Wart", "Skin ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Ptosis", "Malar rash", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Rebound tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Hyperkeratosis", "Decreased level of consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Peripheral edema", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Shock", "Racing thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Keratitis", "Enanthem", "Ventricular tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Skin tag", "Radiculopathy", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Tertiary hyperparathyroidism", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Raynaud's phenomenon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Angina Pectoris", "Chills", "Psychomotor retardation", "Furuncle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Thyroid nodule", "Periorbital puffiness", "Inflammation", "Diplopia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Ptosis", "Wheals", "Upper respiratory tract infection", "Major depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Pretibial myxedema", "Cardiac asthma", "Alopecia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Anemia", "Speech delay", "Oligomenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Heartburn", "Hives", "Shock", "Orofacial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Systemic lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Tetany", "Pericarditis", "Spasticity", "Coagulopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Dysuria", "Speech delay", "Mood swing", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Hemiparesis", "Tonsillitis", "Vaginal odor", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Albuminuria", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Ageusia", "Swollen lymph nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Asymmetry", "Flatulence", "Penile discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Dyspareunia", "Myelopathy", "Clonus", "Nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Wheeze", "Tachylalia", "Hirsutism", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Difficulty walking", "Swollen testicle", "Excessive daytime sleepiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Myelopathy", "Hypercholesterolemia", "Cloudy urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gonorrhea?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Emaciation", "Loss of interest", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Pseudologia fantastica", "Pancreatitis", "Indigestion", "Impulsivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Muehrcke's nails", "Flatulence", "Carelessness", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Failure to thrive", "Lack of Concentration", "Gingival enlargement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Bone pain", "Hyperactivity", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Verbosity", "Hives", "Guilt", "Jaundice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Flu-like syndrome", "Urinary incontinence", "Nikolsky's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Vomiting", "Pelvic pain", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism", "Leukoplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Change in bowel habits", "Middle back pain", "Vaginal bleeding", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Bounding pulse", "Convulsion", "Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Tendonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometrial cancer?", "answers": ["Cough", "Glossitis", "Anterograde amnesia", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Agnosia", "Intertrigo", "Aphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Bounding pulse", "Asymmetry", "Pruritus", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Ageusia", "Difficulty Focusing", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Cerebellar ataxia", "Headache", "Trismus", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Oligomenorrhea", "Obesity", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Weight gain", "Psychosis", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Papule"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Asymmetry", "Formication", "Muscle pain", "Lipodystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Vesicle", "Diaphoresis", "Nocturnal Cough", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Dermatosis", "Neuralgia", "Risus sardonicus", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chickenpox?", "answers": ["Fever", "Bleeding on probing", "Retching", "Peripheral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Cervical cancer", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Edema", "Muscle weakness", "Tachypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Avoidant personality disorder", "Delirium", "Slurred Speech", "Swollen lymph nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Pseudologia fantastica", "Nerve injury", "Difficulty walking", "Skin rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Tetany", "Phyllodes tumor", "Speech delay", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Bruise", "Sputum", "Dry Eye", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Diarrhea", "Mole color changes", "Encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Lymphocytopenia", "Abdominal pain", "Chancre", "Photopsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Hypocalcaemia", "Scleritis", "Fatigue", "Polyphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Fever", "Metabolic acidosis", "Pyuria", "Urinary retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Typhoid fever?", "answers": ["Hyperkeratosis", "Abdominal distension", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Xerophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Paresthesia", "Internal bleeding", "Chorioretinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Panic attack", "Homicidal ideation", "Hepatomegaly", "Medulloblastoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Night Sweats", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Irritability", "Hematochezia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Hunger", "Fatigue", "Photosensitivity", "Bronchiectasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Glycosuria", "Mouth breathing", "Rheumatoid nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Tachypnea", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Hypersexuality", "Eye discharge", "Carelessness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Conjunctivitis", "Headache", "Air crescent sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Insomnia", "Flashback"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Cramp", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Vaginitis", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Leukocytosis", "Speech disorder", "Sore throat", "Rhinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Hives", "Cervical cancer", "Desquamation", "Collapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Blumberg sign", "Bradycardia", "Numbness of the face or tongue", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Indigestion", "Tetany", "Pleuritic chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Pruritus", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "/m/0lxt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Hyperkeratosis", "Hypomimia", "Rumination"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Coma", "Asymptomatic", "Somnolence", "Caput medusae"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Flushing", "Cyst", "Risky behavior", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Hyperreflexia", "Vaginal dryness", "Hypertension", "Myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Dystonia", "Stomatitis", "Muscle Spasms", "Water retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Delayed onset muscle soreness", "Swelling", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Knee pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Xerostomia", "Pain behind the eyes", "Dementia", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Substance abuse", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Glycosuria", "Tinnitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Air crescent sign", "Sneeze", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Tetany", "Bloating", "Kaposi's sarcoma", "Disinhibition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Rheumatoid nodule", "Intermittent claudication", "Dieting", "Jaundice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Xerostomia", "Eczema", "Phonological deficit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Bruise", "Nephritic syndrome", "Heartburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Menorrhagia", "Delirium", "Aphasia", "Thought disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Radiculopathy", "Lightheadedness", "Polyphagia", "Dacryoadenitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Catatonia", "Back pain", "Psychomotor retardation", "Emaciation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Weight gain", "Lack of empathy", "Rumination", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Formication", "Somnolence", "Bouchard's nodes", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Sinusitis", "Fetor hepaticus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Sexual dysfunction", "Infection", "Anterograde amnesia", "Nosebleed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Irregular menstruation", "Stuttering", "Bradykinesia", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Night Sweats", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Skin rash", "Numbness of the face or tongue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Loss of interest", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Risky behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Rectal prolapse", "Syncope", "Bubo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Nuchal Rigidity", "Arthritis", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Dysphonia", "Portal hypertension", "Stroke", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Pus", "Fecal incontinence", "Hypertriglyceridemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Crackles", "Rectal pain", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Goitre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Depression", "Runny nose", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Urinary Frequency", "Hypothermia", "Tachypnea", "Oligomenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Parkinsonism", "Hypercholesterolemia", "Parosmia", "Grandiose delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Breast lump", "Phyllodes tumor", "Amenorrhoea", "Anterograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Pelvic pain", "Torticollis", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Abdominal obesity", "Snoring", "Dysphoria", "Ataxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Substance abuse", "Chest Tightness", "Dysphagia", "Penile discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypothyroidism?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Dyskinesia", "Sinusitis", "Hypocalcaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Dysosmia", "Diarrhea", "Amenorrhoea", "Cachexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Hyperreflexia", "Nuchal Rigidity", "Nerve injury", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Opisthotonus", "Mental illness", "Jaundice", "Iritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Auditory hallucination", "Speech delay", "Indigestion", "Hyperactivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Dyspnea", "Hearing problem", "Hives"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Dupuytren's contracture", "Dysgeusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Intrusive thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Quadriplegia", "Night Sweats", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Glossitis", "Glossitis", "cerebella tumor", "Acute abdomen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Weight loss", "Menorrhagia", "Stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Numbness", "Bigger mole diameter", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Skin tag", "Myerson's sign", "Syncope", "Necrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Nasal polyp", "Aggression", "Bleeding", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Nocturnal enuresis", "Hallucination", "Metrorrhagia", "Tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Difficulty walking", "Back pain", "Skin rash", "Maculopapular rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Night terror", "Furuncle", "Anhidrosis", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Swollen tonsils", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Abdominal distension", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Flaccid paralysis", "Steatorrhea", "Keratitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Rumination", "Uremia", "Kussmaul's sign", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Kehr's sign", "Vomiting", "Petechia", "Levine's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Cramp", "Rebound tenderness", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Hyperkalemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Cullen's sign", "Pharyngitis", "Disinhibition", "Anal swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Kussmaul's sign", "Delayed puberty", "Lymphocytopenia", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Sadness", "Bleeding diathesis", "Dandruff", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Abscess", "Inferiority complex", "Globus pharyngis", "Menorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Pale feces", "Crackles", "Urinary incontinence", "Gynecomastia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Cervicitis", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Osler's sign", "Red eye", "Nipple discharge", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Urinary Frequency", "Bone fracture", "Dyskinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Irregular menstruation", "Intrusive thoughts", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Grey Turner's sign", "Cirrhosis", "Hypercholesterolemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Shivering", "Bell's palsy", "Metrorrhagia", "Anal fissure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Uterine fibroid?", "answers": ["Apnea", "Constipation", "Leukoplakia", "Hypomimia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Intestinal varices", "Medulloblastoma", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Narcissism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Mania", "Abdominal pain", "Hypoglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Hypersexuality", "Gastric varices", "Dizziness", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Auditory hallucination", "Bounding pulse", "Fatigue", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Urinary tract infection", "Dark urine", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Toe walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Hepatic encephalopathy", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Watery eyes", "Flushing", "Anorexia", "Goitre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Tetany", "Muscle pain", "Micrographia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Blackout", "Fever", "Sputum", "Burning Chest Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Chronic pain", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Pulsus paradoxus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Dysentery", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Flatulence", "Acute abdomen", "Ascites", "Quadriplegia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Candidiasis", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Cervical cancer", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Nikolsky's sign", "Thrombocytopenia", "Cyanosis", "Stiff neck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Anhidrosis", "Nausea", "Heart failure", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Nerve injury", "Oral candidiasis", "Vomiting", "Ritualistic behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Sundowning", "Esophageal varices", "Lethargy", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis C?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Bronchiectasis", "Nerve injury", "Anal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "cerebella tumor", "Waxy flexibility", "Dysmenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Dysosmia", "Speech delay", "Cough", "Erythema chronicum migrans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Urinary Frequency", "Lipodystrophy", "Bunion", "Hemoptysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Synovitis", "Verbosity", "Ptosis", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Loss of interest", "Infection", "Vertigo", "Erythema nodosum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Vomiting", "Osler's sign", "Avolition", "Hypersalivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Rhonchi", "Abdominal pain", "Vaginal bleeding", "Stridor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Genital ulcer", "Paresthesia", "Arthritis", "Convulsion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Opportunistic infection", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Pectus carinatum", "Sleep disturbances"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Avolition", "Nephritic syndrome", "Chorioretinitis", "Asymmetry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Uveitis", "Spasmodic dysphonia", "Bone fracture", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Sweating", "Dysphagia", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Myxedema", "Urinary Frequency", "Kaposi's sarcoma", "Hypertonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Asterixis", "Nightmare", "Facial swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Bleeding on probing", "Swollen lymph nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Emaciation", "Blumberg sign", "Alopecia", "Gait abnormality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Peripheral edema", "Postural instability", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Mood swing", "Crackles", "Dementia", "Immunodeficiency"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Polyneuropathy", "Lack of Concentration", "Fatigue", "Hypercapnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Mouth breathing", "Weight loss", "Malaise", "Hematemesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Personality or behavior changes", "Seizure", "Hyperkeratosis", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Bradypnea", "Nocturnal enuresis", "Avolition", "Cachexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Odynophagia", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Echolalia", "Risky behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Narrow stools", "Bradypnea", "Cotton wool spots", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Vaginal dryness", "Catatonia", "Vital Exhaustion", "Spasticity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Diabetes mellitus", "Horner's syndrome", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Candidiasis", "Mastodynia", "Polyphagia", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Bell's palsy", "Anhidrosis", "Hives", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Lymphocytopenia", "Bounding pulse", "Hepatorenal syndrome", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Orofacial pain", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Flushing", "Vision loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Markle sign", "Cervical cancer", "Rheumatoid nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Pressure of speech", "Penile discharge", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Dysphonia", "Hyperaemia", "Night Sweats", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Hyperhidrosis", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Abscess", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Crackles", "Jaundice", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Night terror", "Malocclusion", "Bleeding on probing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Desquamation", "Bleeding gums", "Bacterial vaginosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Spasticity", "Nausea", "Hunger", "Terry's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Nail clubbing", "Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Oral candidiasis", "Pneumatosis intestinalis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Scotoma", "Skin lesion", "Hemiplegia", "Polydipsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Heberden's node", "Change in sexual interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Forgetfulness", "Anhedonia", "Weight gain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Stiffness", "Coma", "Psoas sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Low-grade fever", "Flaccid paralysis", "Dementia", "Tophus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of AIDS?", "answers": ["Fever", "Pressure of speech", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Hyperaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Insomnia?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Osler's sign", "Sleep deprivation", "Pathological laughing and crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Gingival recession", "Oral candidiasis", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Syncope"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Dysphoria", "Lethargy", "Rectal tenesmus", "Schizophasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Gingival recession", "Chest Tightness", "Dizziness", "Disinhibition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Hypotension", "High Fever", "Kussmaul's sign", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Swollen feet", "Albuminuria", "Nerve injury", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Somnolence", "Hemoptysis", "Postural instability", "Abnormal vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Dandruff", "Optic neuritis", "Enophthalmia", "Photosensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Xeroderma", "Hegar's sign", "Grandiose delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Scotoma", "Acalculia", "Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Xerophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Polydipsia", "Iron deficiency", "Golden S sign", "Eczema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Telangiectasia", "Fatigue", "Monomelic amyotrophy", "Anhedonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dehydration?", "answers": ["Feeling of impending doom", "Leukorrhea", "Xerostomia", "Dysphoria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Gingival recession", "Tophus", "Bell's palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Tendonitis", "Petechia", "Keratitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Enuresis", "Menorrhagia", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Tinnitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Bubo", "Polyuria", "Pneumonia", "Flatulence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Flushing", "Hiccup", "Desquamation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Risky behavior", "Abdominal pain", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Polyuria", "Abdominal obesity", "Blister"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lactose intolerance?", "answers": ["Increased vaginal discharge", "Bleeding", "Toothache", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Middle back pain", "Tremor", "Middle back pain", "Syncope"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Hyperacusis", "Dry Eye", "Dieting", "Mania"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Golden S sign", "Osteophyte", "Lightheadedness", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Xerostomia", "Skin ulcer", "Water retention", "Cold sensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Homicidal ideation", "Emaciation", "Enanthem", "Sleep disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Speech delay", "Blank Stare", "Hematoma", "Osteoporosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Headache", "Radiculopathy", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Bruise", "Rose spots", "Ecchymosis", "Grandiose delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Hyperacusis", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Rectal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Racing thoughts", "Hypocalcaemia", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Guilt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Pericarditis", "Frontal release sign", "Extreme Weight Loss", "Choreoathetosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Chemosis", "Erythema multiforme", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Markle sign", "Stridor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anorexia nervosa?", "answers": ["Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Quadriplegia", "Metrorrhagia", "Stunted growth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Halitosis", "Lack of empathy", "Chills", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Nerve injury", "Bradycardia", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Globus pharyngis", "Loss of smell", "Spasmodic dysphonia", "Hematuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Cloudy urine", "Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Knee pain", "Bell's palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Change in sexual interest", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Atrophy", "Bone tumor", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Narrow stools"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Peripheral edema", "Hypocalcaemia", "Nausea", "Halos around lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Dysuria", "Skin tag", "Feeling of impending doom", "Panic attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Pain", "Vaginal tenderness", "Excessive daytime sleepiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Kidney Stone?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Foul smelling urine", "Goitre", "Itchy eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Papule", "Dysarthria", "Stiff neck", "Froment's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Slurred Speech", "Labored breathing", "Osler's sign", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Floater", "Hyperreflexia", "Swollen lymph nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Blood in stool", "Colitis", "Muscle atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Astasia-abasia", "Fasciculation", "Sadness", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Osteophyte", "Monomelic amyotrophy", "Skin Discoloration", "Phlebitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Hematospermia", "Enophthalmia", "Spasticity", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Chest Tightness", "Feeling of impending doom", "Koilonychia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Opportunistic infection", "Muscle Spasms", "Hypokinesia", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Hyperesthesia", "Nausea", "Frequent urination"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Eructation", "Anger", "Substance-related disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Glabellar reflex", "Dehydration", "Mood swing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Skin rash", "Uveitis", "Metrorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Paralysis", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Hyperkalemia", "Irregular menstruation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Paget's disease of the breast", "Blepharospasm", "/m/0lxt", "Vaginal dryness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Pus", "Sleep disturbances", "Wart", "Grandiose delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Hypoxia", "Obturator sign", "Mastodynia", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Menopause?", "answers": ["Hot flash", "Joint stiffness", "Dystonia", "Decreased level of consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital wart?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Eructation", "Pain", "Acute bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital wart?", "answers": ["Blepharospasm", "Brittle nails", "Vaginal bleeding", "Hypercapnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital wart?", "answers": ["Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Lactose intolerance", "Papule", "Blackout"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital wart?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Desquamation", "Bleeding", "Lumbago"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Cloudy urine", "Nausea", "Glycosuria", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Bronchiectasis", "Dizziness", "Hypomania", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Fatigue", "Wheeze", "Hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Scleritis", "Blumberg sign", "Sexual dysfunction", "Fourth heart sound"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Hematochezia", "Dysmenorrhea", "Bradypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Neck pain", "Dissociative disorder", "Gait abnormality", "Dysmenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Urinary tract infection", "Hypotension", "Flatulence", "Psoas sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Depression", "Eructation", "Pulmonary edema", "Myopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Fox's sign", "Dystonia", "Psoas sign", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Pain", "Hormonal disorders", "Pain behind the eyes", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Nephrotic syndrome", "Pruritus ani", "Glossitis", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Intermittent claudication", "Leukoplakia", "Nausea", "Disinhibition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Indigestion", "Flushing", "Erectile dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Heart murmur", "Leukocytosis", "Eye pain", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Hemoperitoneum", "Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Lightheadedness", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Angina Pectoris?", "answers": ["Lymphocytopenia", "Hemoptysis", "Chest Tightness", "Levine's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Night terror", "Mole color changes", "Dysphonia", "Groin Lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Hypoglycemia", "Change in bowel habits", "Nocturnal enuresis", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Shallow breathing", "Maculopapular rash", "Retrograde amnesia", "Hypertriglyceridemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Bradypnea", "Cervicitis", "Eructation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Blood in stool", "Urinary tract infection", "Portal hypertension", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Fourth heart sound", "Waxy flexibility", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Mouth breathing", "Erythroleukoplakia", "Optic neuritis", "Cardiac asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Psychomotor retardation", "Cirrhosis", "Hypersomnia", "Metabolic acidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Insomnia", "Numbness", "Parkinsonism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Grandiose delusion", "Anuria", "Irritability", "Abdominal distension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Somnolence", "Hypocalcaemia", "Chronic pain", "Purpura"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Slurred Speech", "Vasculitis", "Candidiasis", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Nausea", "Hypercapnia", "Hyperphosphatemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Bruxism", "Toothache", "Trismus", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Crepitus", "Headache", "Shock", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Speech delay", "Vasoconstriction", "Snoring", "Goitre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Photosensitivity", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Microalbuminuria", "Blister"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Skin tag", "Respiratory arrest", "Glabellar reflex", "Sundowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Bronchiectasis", "Major depression", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Bronchospasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Nocturia", "Muscle weakness", "Blepharospasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Mental illness", "Anorexia", "Pain behind the eyes", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Iritis", "Erythema nodosum", "Testicle pain", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Blood in stool", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Feeling of impending doom", "Photophobia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Pruritus ani", "Osteophyte", "Dysphonia", "Rectal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Fatigue", "Irritability", "Dysmenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Hyperlipidemia", "Maculopapular rash", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Ileus", "Nodule", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Chills"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Nosebleed", "Anemia", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Drooling", "Pruritus ani", "Rectal tenesmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Nodule", "Hematochezia", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Ketoacidosis", "Headache", "Dyspnea", "Ventricular tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Major depressive episode", "Heart murmur", "Vomiting", "Loose teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Frontal release sign", "Bleeding", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Muehrcke's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Somnolence", "Ataxia", "Bloating", "Nerve injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Edema", "Hyperglycemia", "Rectal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Asymptomatic", "Breakthrough bleeding", "Balance disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Abdominal mass", "Gait abnormality", "Wart", "Avolition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Cachexia", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Major depressive episode", "Parkinsonism", "Vesical tenesmus", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Narrow stools", "Asymmetry", "Cough", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Deformity", "Mood swing", "Change in bowel habits", "Compulsive hoarding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Paresthesia", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Chills"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Muscle Spasms", "Restless legs syndrome", "Skin ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Conductive hearing loss", "Intestinal varices", "Diarrhea", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Scaly skin", "Tumor", "Bradycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Colorectal cancer?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Koilonychia", "Ritualistic behavior", "Wheeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Hypotension", "Atrophy", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Apraxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Hormonal disorders", "Anhedonia", "Tachypnea", "Sensorineural hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Stridor", "Gingival recession", "Mental confusion", "Bouchard's nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Melancholia", "Cramp", "Apathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Crackles", "Hormonal disorders", "Coma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Frequent urination", "Chills", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Male infertility"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Delusion", "Dandruff", "Nipple tenderness", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Flushing", "Dysphagia", "Akathisia", "Vesicle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Petechia", "Bubo", "Akathisia", "Convulsion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Tonsillitis", "Headache", "Otorrhea", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Oligomenorrhea", "Anhidrosis", "Phlebitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthermia?", "answers": ["Tachycardia", "Cardiac asthma", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Dacryoadenitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Cold sensitivity", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Neck mass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Lymphocytosis", "Pale feces", "Mole color changes", "Abdominal mass"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Bounding pulse", "Dark urine", "Dysphagia", "Menorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Nausea", "Bradykinesia", "Hyperesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Orthostatic hypotension", "Malaise", "Tonsillitis", "Muscle weakness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Stiff neck", "Pruritus", "Sundowning", "Hypomimia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Slurred Speech", "Genital sores", "Difficulty Focusing", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Photosensitivity", "Rose spots", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Back pain", "Fibrosis", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Jaundice?", "answers": ["Grandiose delusion", "Bone tumor", "Mental confusion", "Neuralgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Morphea", "Melena", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Excessive Crying", "Intellectual disability", "Ataxia", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Collapse", "Avolition", "Orthopnea", "Rectal tenesmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Vaginitis", "Stuttering", "Coagulopathy", "Apathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Sleep disturbances", "Sputum", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "High Fever", "Dizziness", "Erythema chronicum migrans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Hepatomegaly", "Chest Tightness", "Dehydration", "Retrograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Anasarca", "Hematoma", "Urinary tract infection", "Cerebellar ataxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Dyspnea", "Vaginal dryness", "Vital Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Sinusitis", "Rheumatoid nodule", "Hyperreflexia", "Peripheral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Skin lesion", "Bell's palsy", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Heart failure?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Cyanosis", "Hypercholesterolemia", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Rectal bleeding", "Micrographia", "Agnosia", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Delayed reading ability", "Hirano body", "Pursed lip breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Gynecomastia", "Fever", "Irregular menstruation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Thought insertion", "Pectus carinatum", "Dacryoadenitis", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Constipation", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Parosmia", "Muscle weakness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Vomiting", "Hepatosplenomegaly", "Anal fissure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Menorrhagia", "Globus pharyngis", "Nausea", "Tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Night Sweats", "Cough", "Hematochezia", "Hematoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Akathisia", "Eye discharge", "Dry cough", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Peripheral edema", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diverticulitis?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "Leukoplakia", "Tinnitus", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Carbon monoxide poisoning?", "answers": ["Mania", "Headache", "Sleep deprivation", "Swollen tonsils"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Lymphocytosis", "Cyanosis", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Apnea", "Metrorrhagia", "Chorioretinitis", "Male infertility"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Erythroleukoplakia", "Furuncle", "Pneumonia", "Excessive daytime sleepiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Mood swing", "Heartburn", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Pulmonary hypertension", "Fetor hepaticus", "Lack of Remorse", "Dysphoria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Nail clubbing", "Vaginitis", "Swelling", "Rhonchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Bone tumor", "Hemoptysis", "Scotoma", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Polyneuropathy", "Halitosis", "Rectal prolapse", "Periorbital puffiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Peripheral edema", "Fasciculation", "Low-grade fever", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Sputum", "Steatorrhea", "Paget's disease of the breast"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Ritualistic behavior", "Stomatitis", "Delayed milestone", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Fecal incontinence", "Cullen's sign", "Deformity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Heart failure", "Excessive Crying", "Quadriplegia", "Verbosity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Postural instability", "Diarrhea", "Erythema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Cyanosis", "Bigger mole diameter", "Nipple discharge", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Acute bronchitis", "Cramp", "Cracked Skin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Dysuria", "Numbness of face"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Excessive Crying", "Swollen legs", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Wheeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Fibromyalgia", "Toe walking", "Numbness of face", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Nasal polyp", "Compulsive behavior", "Hematoma", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Rhonchi", "Risus sardonicus", "Emaciation", "Bronchiectasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Abdominal pain", "Atrophy", "Polyphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cystic fibrosis?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Muscle pain", "Phyllodes tumor", "Phonological deficit"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Metrorrhagia", "Erythema chronicum migrans", "Urinary urgency", "Anal swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Rectal tenesmus", "Tic", "Paresthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Hegar's sign", "Melena", "Pain", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Lipodystrophy", "Asterixis", "Pruritus ani", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Audible pop at time of injury", "Radiculopathy", "Blood in stool", "Ventricular tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Asymmetry", "Lightheadedness", "Stereotypy", "Candidiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Deformity", "Splenomegaly", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Narrow stools"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Rectal pain", "Pancolitis", "Chorioretinitis", "Torticollis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Tertiary hyperparathyroidism", "Verbosity", "Inflammation", "Xerophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Urethritis", "Muscle weakness", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Phlebitis", "Menorrhagia", "Chorioretinitis", "Water-electrolyte imbalance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Necrosis", "Urinary retention", "Thrombosis", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Male infertility", "Urinary incontinence", "Hematochezia", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Neuralgia", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Hematoma", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hemorrhoids?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Quadriplegia", "Gingival recession"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Substance abuse?", "answers": ["Fasciculation", "Vasculitis", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Blackout"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Water retention", "Myerson's sign", "Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Gastric varices"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Chest pain", "Numbness of face", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Fetor hepaticus", "Flatulence", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Asterixis", "Bell's palsy", "Neuralgia", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Rose spots", "Dysmenorrhea", "Homicidal ideation", "Steatorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Dysesthesia", "Testicle pain", "Crepitus", "Urethritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Sadness", "Blackout", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Enophthalmia", "Agitation", "Asymptomatic", "Immunodeficiency"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Fever", "Angular cheilitis", "Myxedema", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Vaginal bleeding", "Scotoma", "Substance-related disorder", "Skin tag"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Irregular menstruation", "Anuria", "Desquamation", "Cullen's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Hemoptysis", "Candidiasis", "Pulsus paradoxus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Enophthalmia", "Emaciation", "Urge incontinence", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Stupor", "Menorrhagia", "Astasia-abasia", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Sweating", "Cramp", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Tonsillitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Risky behavior", "Dysuria", "Avolition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pelvic inflammatory disease?", "answers": ["Abdominal mass", "Paralysis", "Periorbital puffiness", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Stiffness", "Nausea", "Type 2 diabetes", "Terry's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Pharyngitis", "Fetor hepaticus", "Nail clubbing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Bronchiectasis", "Sweating", "Abdominal mass", "Trousseau sign of malignancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Spider angioma", "Anhedonia", "Hyperhidrosis", "Neck mass"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Hydrocele", "Grey Turner's sign", "Gingivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Anal swelling", "Syncope", "Bleeding on probing", "Glycosuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Pharyngitis", "Vomiting", "Slurred Speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Chancre", "Muscle Spasms", "Fatigue", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Abdominal aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Globus pharyngis", "Back pain", "Water retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Postural instability", "Spider angioma", "Back pain", "Urinary retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Dysautonomia", "Inferiority complex", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Homicidal ideation", "Hyperkeratosis", "Pectus carinatum", "Rhonchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Phonological deficit", "Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Vomiting", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Phlegm", "Bronchiectasis", "Conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Wart", "Hypoglycemia", "Nasal congestion", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Wheeze", "Skin rash", "Telangiectasia", "Conductive hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Inverted nipple", "Boredom", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Silhouette sign", "Cough", "Speech delay", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Shock", "Erythema", "Fatigue", "Self-harm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Vaginal discharge", "Retrograde amnesia", "Narcissism", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Hematospermia", "Dyspnea", "Psychomotor retardation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Asterixis", "Pathological laughing and crying", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Glossodynia", "Angular cheilitis", "Chills", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Dysuria", "Stunted growth", "Bronchospasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Loss of smell", "Abdominal pain", "Hypomania", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Thrombocytopenia", "Sputum", "Emotional insecurity", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Sleep deprivation", "Nipple discharge", "Vasculitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Tachycardia", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Diarrhea", "Eye discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Compulsive behavior", "Vaginal bleeding", "Fox's sign", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Caput medusae", "Facial pain", "Delusion", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bronchitis?", "answers": ["Failure to thrive", "Sore throat", "Esophageal varices", "Muehrcke's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Hypertension", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Synovitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Thyroid nodule", "Parkinsonism", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Conjunctivitis", "Polyneuropathy", "Mental confusion", "Koilonychia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Coma", "Tachypnea", "Foul smelling urine", "Gingival recession"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Frequent urination", "Swollen testicle", "Central facial palsy", "Rovsing's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Metrorrhagia", "Difficulty walking", "Granuloma", "Convulsion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Painful ejaculation", "Feeling of impending doom", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Pectus carinatum", "Diplopia", "Jaundice", "Paraphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Leukopenia", "Nephritic syndrome", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Joint stiffness", "Nystagmus", "Astasia-abasia", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Hypersomnia", "Apraxia", "Renal colic", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Nystagmus", "Polyuria", "Aphasia", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Self-harm", "Tenderness", "Oral bleeding", "Enanthem"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Vesical tenesmus", "Tinnitus", "Fatty liver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Phyllodes tumor", "Alopecia", "Urinary Frequency", "Dysuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Laryngitis", "Bleeding", "Costovertebral angle tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Fever", "Hyperventilation", "Stuttering"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Dystonia", "Burning Chest Pain", "Change in bowel habits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Grey Turner's sign", "Abdominal pain", "Vaginal tenderness", "Gait abnormality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Fourth heart sound", "Spinal tumor", "Anger", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Red eye", "Dysesthesia", "Purpura"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Enuresis", "Hirsutism", "Malocclusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Urinary urgency", "Indigestion", "Weight loss", "Grandiose delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Acute abdomen", "Genital ulcer", "Irritability", "Silhouette sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Vaginal dryness", "Swelling", "Ageusia", "Azotemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Visual verbal agnosia", "Gait abnormality", "Nausea", "Feeling of impending doom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Muehrcke's nails", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Chills", "Gingival recession", "Lack of Remorse", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Bone pain", "Vaginitis", "Bell's palsy", "Necrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Emaciation", "Hunger", "Hyperpigmentation", "Pyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Ecchymosis", "Leukocytosis", "Dactylitis", "Homicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Oliguria", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Bradykinesia", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Infertility", "Hypersalivation", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Papule", "Genital ulcer", "Spasmodic dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pyelonephritis?", "answers": ["Hematuria", "Excessive Crying", "Erythema chronicum migrans", "Muscle atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Apnea", "Scotoma", "Tumor", "Self-harm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Nipple tenderness", "Oral candidiasis", "Substance-related disorder", "Hallucination"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Dark urine", "Breast lump", "Anterograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Facial nerve paralysis", "Phlebitis", "Seborrheic dermatitis", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Anasarca", "Parosmia", "Inverted nipple", "Irregular menstruation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Genital ulcer", "Pain", "Retrograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Swollen legs", "Gingivitis", "Edema", "Nipple discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Enanthem", "Glycosuria", "Myxedema", "Paget's disease of the breast"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Hypoxemia", "Convulsion", "Erythema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Crackles", "Phyllodes tumor", "Dissociative disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Breast cancer?", "answers": ["Aggression", "Hot flash", "Conjunctivitis", "Cotton wool spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Enuresis", "Enanthem", "Esophageal varices", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Bronchophony", "Rectal tenesmus", "Numbness of the face or tongue", "Eye discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Constipation", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Change in sexual interest", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Bradykinesia", "Lactose intolerance", "Hyperaemia", "Anhedonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Conjunctivitis?", "answers": ["Chemosis", "Bruxism", "Hypogonadism", "Erectile dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Bigger mole diameter", "Anorexia", "Pharyngitis", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Bigger mole diameter", "Night Sweats", "Medulloblastoma", "Genital ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Chorioretinitis", "Fatigue", "Palpitation", "Spasmodic dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Globus pharyngis", "Pruritus", "Asymmetry", "Stunted growth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Diaphoresis", "Tenderness", "Proctitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Swollen lymph nodes", "Blood in stool", "Cervical cancer", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hodgkin's lymphoma?", "answers": ["Hypersomnia", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Rovsing's sign", "Amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Photosensitivity", "Asymptomatic", "Granuloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Metabolic acidosis", "Acne", "Genital ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Hypoxemia", "Blumberg sign", "Tumor", "Pain behind the eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Hyperreflexia", "Hypoxia", "Pruritus", "Hypokinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Genital wart", "Bradykinesia", "Breast lump", "Cardiac asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Mental confusion", "Hyperreflexia", "Polyneuropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Human papillomavirus infection?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Wart", "Encephalopathy", "Vertigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of HIV?", "answers": ["Obturator sign", "Blepharospasm", "Sore throat", "Lactose intolerance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Delirium", "Parosmia", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Hirano body", "Vomiting", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Polyneuropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Anhedonia", "Koilonychia", "Inflammation", "Blank Stare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Sexual dysfunction", "Polyuria", "Nausea", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Cullen's sign", "Groin Lump", "Euphoria", "Clonus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Constipation", "Intrusive thoughts", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Anhedonia", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Inguinal hernia?", "answers": ["Rebound tenderness", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Social isolation", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Syncope", "Fever", "Hunger", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Hallucination", "Hypocalcaemia", "Chills", "Water-electrolyte imbalance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Infection", "Pica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Hypomania", "Headache", "Hypercapnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Fatigue", "Markle sign", "Anhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Suicidal ideation", "Amnesia", "Genital ulcer", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Medulloblastoma", "Bouchard's nodes", "Impetigo", "Sore throat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Hyperreflexia", "Lack of Concentration", "Tremor", "Cloudy urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Apraxia", "Oliguria", "Xeroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Menorrhagia", "Paraphasia", "Muscle Spasms", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic fatigue syndrome?", "answers": ["Itchy eyes", "Mastodynia", "Chancre", "Vital Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Lightheadedness", "Chills", "Hutchinson's sign", "Foul smelling urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Scotoma", "Obturator sign", "Candidiasis", "Vertigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Deafness", "Anal discharge", "Dupuytren's contracture", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Blurred vision", "Kehr's sign", "Tendonitis", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Vomiting", "Rovsing's sign", "Cramp", "Bone tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo?", "answers": ["Orthopnea", "Nausea", "Lymphocytopenia", "Palmar erythema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Swollen legs", "Tachylalia", "Leukoplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Pancolitis", "Vomiting", "Body ache", "Abdominal obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Penile discharge", "Abdominal obesity", "Sore throat", "Hunger"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Fever", "Markle sign", "Xeroderma", "Dysarthria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Kehr's sign", "Renal colic", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Otorrhea", "Poor wound healing", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Hypokinesia", "Rectal pain", "Oral candidiasis", "Necrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Lhermitte's sign", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Leukocytosis", "Cullen's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Swollen tonsils", "Angular cheilitis", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anaphylaxis?", "answers": ["Peripheral neuropathy", "Skin rash", "Syncope", "Nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anaphylaxis?", "answers": ["Hypotension", "Hearing problem", "Chest pain", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Lightheadedness", "Seizure", "Lymphocytosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Keratitis", "Cirrhosis", "Bone tumor", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Tophus", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Headache", "Hemoptysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Irritability", "Loose teeth", "Delirium", "Diplopia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Hormonal disorders", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Dysgeusia", "Urinary tract infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Kaposi's sarcoma", "Dyspnea", "Nausea", "Purpura"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Acute bronchitis", "Hyperlipidemia", "Mental confusion", "Horner's syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Hemoptysis", "Maculopapular rash", "Oligomenorrhea", "Tunnel vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Silhouette sign", "Vomiting", "Urinary incontinence", "Gynecologic hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Eye pain", "Otorrhea", "Apraxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Personality or behavior changes", "Monomelic amyotrophy", "Breast lump", "Lack of empathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Auditory hallucination", "Balance disorder", "Anal discharge", "Esophageal varices"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Brain tumor?", "answers": ["Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Diabetes mellitus", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Hearing problem"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pleurisy?", "answers": ["Chills", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Genital wart", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pleurisy?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine", "Blurred vision", "Groin Lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pleurisy?", "answers": ["Bacterial vaginosis", "Coma", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pleurisy?", "answers": ["Astasia-abasia", "Blank Stare", "High Fever", "Dry cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pleurisy?", "answers": ["Anasarca", "Racing thoughts", "Chest pain", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Renal failure?", "answers": ["Hepatic encephalopathy", "Hypotension", "Sleep deprivation", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Psychosis", "Rose spots", "Shock", "Apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Loss of interest", "Nausea", "Intestinal varices", "Dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Osteoporosis", "Rectal prolapse", "Bleeding gums", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Psychosis", "Headache", "Meningism", "Vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Vomiting", "Numbness of the face or tongue", "Vaginal dryness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Delirium", "Tetany", "Delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Salmonellosis?", "answers": ["Hematochezia", "Abscess", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Hunger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Hypoglycemia", "Muscle weakness", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Hepatorenal syndrome", "Narcissism", "Golden S sign", "Conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Floater", "Pharyngitis", "cerebella tumor", "Avoidant personality disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Hypotension", "Hyperkeratosis", "Breast lump", "Sneeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Iron deficiency", "Shivering", "Neck mass", "Change in sexual interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Photophobia", "Lipodystrophy", "Gynecomastia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Sundowning", "Major depression", "Bubo", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Compulsive hoarding", "Hirano body", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Coagulopathy", "Cyst", "Hot flash", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Poor wound healing", "Vaginal dryness", "Vesical tenesmus", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Blepharospasm", "Flatulence", "Cough", "Extreme Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["Pathological laughing and crying", "Pancreatitis", "Rhinitis", "Pectus carinatum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Common cold?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Muscle pain", "Loose teeth", "Urethritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Colitis", "Pallor", "Dyspareunia", "Polydipsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Ketoacidosis", "Cervicitis", "Hyperactivity", "Polyphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Peripheral neuropathy", "Neck mass", "Gingivitis", "Ileus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Poor wound healing", "Halos around lights", "Leg pain", "Kaposi's sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Dysautonomia", "Blurred vision", "Stereotypy", "Wheals"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Infection", "Dysautonomia", "Heartburn", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Pancolitis", "Markle sign", "Polyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Prediabetes?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Chest pain", "Hypocalcaemia", "Hyperglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Gingivitis", "Anemia", "Tunnel vision", "Rovsing's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Leukopenia", "Narcissism", "Extreme Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Hypokinesia", "Homicidal ideation", "Abdominal mass", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Stroke", "Waxy flexibility", "Thrombocytopenia", "Visual verbal agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Neck mass", "Painless testicular lump", "Intertrigo", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Night Sweats", "Sleep deprivation", "Fibrosis", "Psychosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Inflammation", "Alopecia", "Loss of smell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Hypercholesterolemia", "Malar rash", "Clouding of consciousness", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Ritualistic behavior", "Hypercholesterolemia", "Nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Splenomegaly", "Cardiac asthma", "Spinal tumor", "Bronchophony"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Biliary colic", "Pulmonary edema", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Tendonitis", "Vasculitis", "Substance-related disorder", "Lymphocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Papule", "Bruxism", "Melena", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Ascites", "Osteophyte", "Major depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Fever", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Mastodynia", "Hepatomegaly", "Delayed milestone", "Eosinophilia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Necrosis", "Tumor", "Dysosmia", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Orofacial pain", "Headache", "Short stature", "Dieting"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Odynophagia", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Ageusia", "Hematochezia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Lymphocytosis", "Pulmonary edema", "Proteinuria", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lymphoma?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Carelessness", "Anorexia", "Asterixis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetic neuropathy?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Proctitis", "Paresthesia", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Fibrosis", "Nasal congestion", "Forgetfulness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Hypomimia", "Watery eyes", "Blumberg sign", "Amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Hyperlipidemia", "Facial nerve paralysis", "Anorexia", "Grey Turner's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Disregard for right and wrong", "Malocclusion", "Toothache", "Rhinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Anal fissure", "Hirsutism", "Sneeze", "Azotemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Myxedema", "Fever", "Spasticity", "Melancholia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pertussis?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Dry cough", "Sexual obsessions", "Skin lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Enanthem", "Frontal release sign", "Nausea", "Nervousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Acalculia", "Vasoconstriction", "Muscle atrophy", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Tumor", "Hyperglycemia", "Post-nasal drip", "Retrograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Cyst", "Hirsutism", "Rectal bleeding", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Leukorrhea", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Boredom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Intestinal varices", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Anemia", "Cachexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Rectal bleeding", "Inferiority complex", "Quadriplegia", "Abdominal mass"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Rectal pain", "Steatorrhea", "Thought disorder", "Hypomimia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Choreoathetosis", "Erythema nodosum", "Heartburn", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Middle back pain", "Heberden's node", "Racing thoughts", "Risky behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Delayed onset muscle soreness", "Diarrhea", "Numbness of face", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Periorbital puffiness", "Glycosuria", "Vomiting", "Mood swing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Rectal prolapse", "Tonsillitis", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Delayed puberty", "Vesicle", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Type 2 diabetes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Jaundice", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Chancre"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Quadriplegia", "Granuloma", "Impetigo", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Angina Pectoris", "Dissociative disorder", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Hyperphosphatemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Hematemesis", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Vaginal dryness", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Cyanosis", "Sputum", "Eye discharge", "Ascites"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Fibrosis", "Mood swing", "Diabetes mellitus", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pancreatic cancer?", "answers": ["Bleeding gums", "Gingival enlargement", "Shivering", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Autism?", "answers": ["Self-harm", "Pretibial myxedema", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Chorioretinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Autism?", "answers": ["Emotional insecurity", "Stereotypy", "Groin Lump", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Autism?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Stunted growth", "Astasia-abasia", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Autism?", "answers": ["Fibromyalgia", "Scotoma", "Compulsive behavior", "Anasarca"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Autism?", "answers": ["Bruxism", "Hyperesthesia", "Ritualistic behavior", "Dizziness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Odynophagia", "Psychomotor retardation", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Dacryoadenitis", "Swollen testicle", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Sneeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Breast lump", "Nausea", "Psychosis", "Mood swing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Runny nose", "Urge incontinence", "Guilt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Anal fissure", "Loss of smell", "Dysgeusia", "Sleep apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Vesical tenesmus", "Nasal congestion", "Carelessness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Orofacial pain", "Hypoxia", "Chemosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Genital wart", "Abdominal distension", "Neck pain", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Risky behavior", "Toothache", "Metabolic acidosis", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Nerve injury", "Nipple tenderness", "Night Sweats", "Facial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Headache", "Maculopapular rash", "Jaundice", "Thyrotoxicosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Post-void dribbling", "Post-nasal drip", "Retching", "Catatonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Fever", "Oliguria", "Inverted nipple"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Bladder spasm", "Halitosis", "Syncope", "Carelessness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Hepatosplenomegaly", "Hemiparesis", "Fatigue", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sinusitis?", "answers": ["Spider angioma", "Irritability", "Lightheadedness", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Bleeding", "Hypertonia", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Loss Of Consciousness", "Rhonchi", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Ileus", "Clouding of consciousness", "Stroke", "Carpal tunnel syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Headache", "Acne", "Bleeding on probing", "Pelvic inflammatory disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Vaginal dryness", "Night terror", "Delayed onset muscle soreness", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Vision disorder", "Middle back pain", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intracranial aneurysm?", "answers": ["Barrel chest", "Rovsing's sign", "Frequent urination", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Crackles", "Wandering", "Lhermitte's sign", "Swollen tonsils"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Body ache", "Synovitis", "Phlegm", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Diabetes mellitus", "Osteophyte", "Chills", "Shivering"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Dry Eye", "Joint stiffness", "Swelling", "Apnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Micrographia", "Osler's sign", "Fever", "Bone Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Water retention", "Pelvic pain", "Erectile dysfunction", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Racing thoughts", "Loss of interest", "Abdominal obesity", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Social isolation", "Intellectual disability", "Runny nose", "Akathisia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Nosebleed", "Rectal pain", "Sore throat", "Muehrcke's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Hematuria", "Glossitis", "Cotton wool spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Wheeze", "Nail clubbing", "Hypertension", "Pathological laughing and crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Rovsing's sign", "Frequent urination", "Laryngitis", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Rhonchi", "Constipation", "Tonsillitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Nasal polyp", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Hemoptysis", "Urinary tract infection", "Splenomegaly", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Bounding pulse", "Dissociative disorder", "Cough", "Hepatorenal syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Hives", "Nosebleed", "Dyspnea", "Dysphoria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute bronchitis?", "answers": ["Uveitis", "Cardiac asthma", "Nodule", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Orthopnea", "Risky behavior", "Hepatorenal syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Pale feces", "Eczema", "Cyst", "Red eye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Blurred vision", "Vaginal bleeding", "Xerophthalmia", "Cold sensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Eye pain", "Leukocytosis", "Indigestion", "Hot flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Tunnel vision", "Barrel chest", "Flashback", "Stupor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Vomiting", "Anterograde amnesia", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Glaucoma?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Myelopathy", "Nausea", "Myopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Hyperpigmentation", "Cramp", "Metabolic acidosis", "Skin tag"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Pale feces", "Obesity", "Astasia-abasia", "Mania"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Retching", "Dacryoadenitis", "Inverted nipple", "Keratitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Cold sensitivity", "Keratitis", "Swollen feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Back pain", "Jaundice", "Urethritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Urethritis", "Nodule", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Flashback", "Chills", "Mental illness", "Palmar erythema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Headache", "Dysarthria", "Rheumatoid nodule", "Dacryoadenitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Blood in stool", "Hot flash", "Muehrcke's nails", "Orthostatic hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Sadness", "Syncope", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Odynophagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Hyperventilation", "Narrow stools", "Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Disinhibition", "Vomiting", "Vaginal discharge", "Fibromyalgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Formication", "Pulmonary edema", "Pharyngitis", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Flatulence", "Opisthotonus", "Stomatitis", "Sexual dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Jaundice", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Muscle Spasms", "Uremia", "Lipodystrophy", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Nipple discharge", "Hyperphosphatemia", "Bloating", "Fatty liver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Microalbuminuria", "Bacterial vaginosis", "Anterograde amnesia", "Muscle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Enophthalmia", "Heart failure", "Muscle weakness", "Somnolence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Vital Exhaustion", "Colitis", "Leukocytosis", "Hypomania"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Oligomenorrhea", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Flashback"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Myopathy", "Respiratory arrest", "Fever", "Nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Hypoglycemia", "Stereotypy", "Nausea", "Waxy flexibility"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Nephrotic syndrome", "Stroke", "Abdominal distension", "Swollen testicle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Pectus carinatum", "Internal bleeding", "Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Low-grade fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Gingival recession", "Hypersomnia", "Periorbital puffiness", "Indigestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroenteritis?", "answers": ["Hirano body", "Short stature", "Eructation", "Gingival enlargement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Oliguria", "Chronic cough", "Heart murmur", "Terry's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Anuria", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Blank Stare", "Laryngitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Costovertebral angle tenderness", "Fibrosis", "Metabolic acidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute renal failure?", "answers": ["Compulsive hoarding", "Pruritus ani", "Hyperkalemia", "Acute abdomen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Kussmaul's sign", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Dyschezia", "Glycosuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Self-destructive behaviour", "Irregular menstruation", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Thyroid nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Pelvic pain", "Diabetes mellitus", "Frequent urination", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Infertility", "Hypomania", "Agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Nausea", "Chancre", "Dysuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Ageusia", "Hypothermia", "Dysmenorrhea", "Hot flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Post-nasal drip", "Cachexia", "Male infertility", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Endometriosis?", "answers": ["Phyllodes tumor", "Gait abnormality", "Abdominal pain", "Scotoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Swollen lymph nodes", "Auditory hallucination", "Koilonychia", "Xerostomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Phonological deficit", "Psychomotor retardation", "Abdominal pain", "Nipple tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Neuralgia", "Irritability", "Runny nose", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Post-nasal drip", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Social isolation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Panic attack", "Silhouette sign", "Lack of empathy", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Lack of empathy", "Syncope", "Disregard for right and wrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Pyuria", "Intestinal varices", "Barrel chest", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Astasia-abasia", "Apathy", "Tree-in-bud sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Frontal release sign", "Pruritus ani", "Sadness", "Hyperventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Paranoia", "Pus", "Nodule", "Air crescent sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Palpitation", "Myelopathy", "Verbosity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Renal colic", "Flushing", "Emotional insecurity", "Malocclusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Chest pain", "Dysphonia", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Kehr's sign", "Thrombocytopenia", "Paresthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Chills", "Lack of Remorse", "Bruxism", "Lower motor neuron lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Candidiasis", "Hypervigilance", "Tunnel vision", "Parosmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Radiculopathy", "Constipation", "Oliguria", "Post-nasal drip"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Petechia", "Renal failure", "Lightheadedness", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Hematemesis", "Tachycardia", "Dandruff", "Diplopia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Pain", "Chemosis", "Ventricular tachycardia", "Bacterial vaginosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Vesical tenesmus", "Headache", "Nocturia", "Golden S sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Shallow breathing", "Ritualistic behavior", "Nightmare", "Polyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Diplopia", "Medulloblastoma", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Angular cheilitis", "Deformity", "Hydrocele"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Psoas sign", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Granuloma", "Lumbago"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "Urinary incontinence", "Palmar erythema", "Sleep disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Failure to thrive", "Hematochezia", "Intrusive thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Hot flash", "Hepatosplenomegaly", "Wart", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Feeling of impending doom", "Heart murmur", "Anterograde amnesia", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Bladder spasm", "Post-nasal drip", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Cough", "Inverted nipple", "Facial pain", "Globus pharyngis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic attack?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Pale feces", "Shivering", "Hypokinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Malocclusion", "Bone fracture", "Pelvic pain", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Flaccid paralysis", "Wheeze", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Indigestion", "Cramp", "High Fever", "Cachexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Anal swelling", "Fatigue", "Delayed puberty", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Psychosis", "Constipation", "Bounding pulse", "Bunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Abdominal pain", "Hypertension", "Change in bowel habits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Vaginal bleeding", "Bunion", "Leukoplakia", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Bloating", "Tinnitus", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Flashback", "Urinary Frequency", "Bacterial vaginosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Water retention", "Dyspnea", "Tendonitis", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cancer?", "answers": ["Conjunctivitis", "Nausea", "Erythroleukoplakia", "Sleep disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bone fracture?", "answers": ["Chest Tightness", "Weight gain", "Swelling", "Asterixis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Vomiting", "Optic neuritis", "Melanocytic nevus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Fever", "Seizure", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Dyschezia", "Retrograde amnesia", "Metrorrhagia", "Rhinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Miscarriage?", "answers": ["Panic attack", "Cervical cancer", "Sneeze", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Deformity", "Short stature", "Radiculopathy", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Rectal tenesmus", "Grandiose delusion", "Dacryoadenitis", "Orofacial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Psychosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Tinnitus", "Border irregularity", "Schizophasia", "Rectal tenesmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Emotional insecurity", "Gingival recession", "Osler's sign", "Esophageal varices"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Quadriplegia", "Muscle Spasms", "Floater", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Swollen feet", "Leukoplakia", "Ileus", "Pain behind the eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Hyperacusis", "Fatty liver", "Panic attack", "Burning Chest Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Desquamation", "Joint pain", "Stereotypy", "Sweating"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Pulmonary hypertension", "Neck pain", "Intellectual disability", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Telangiectasia", "Trismus", "Coma", "Hyperreflexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Slurred Speech", "Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Hypertension", "Muscle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Tenderness", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Red eye", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Delirium", "Forgetfulness", "Glossodynia", "Tetany"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Flaccid paralysis", "Malocclusion", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Muscle weakness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Toothache", "Vasoconstriction", "Anal swelling", "Dyschezia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Cyst", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Chronic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Headache", "Post-nasal drip", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Vertigo", "Pectus carinatum", "Desquamation", "Pale feces"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Temporomandibular joint dysfunction?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Tetany", "Neuralgia", "Facial Paresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Blumberg sign", "Eosinophilia", "Paresthesia", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Goitre", "Bubo", "Nightmare", "Coma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Lack of Concentration", "Erythroplakia", "Thrombocytopenia", "Waxy flexibility"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Swollen feet", "Delayed reading ability", "Cervicitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Knee pain", "Nausea", "Vaginal dryness", "Erythroplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Retching", "Internal bleeding", "Frontal release sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Vision disorder", "Weight loss", "Polyneuropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Paranoia", "Vertigo", "Nikolsky's sign", "Spider angioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Neuralgia", "Dieting"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Inferiority complex", "Tachycardia", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Bone pain", "Polydipsia", "Stridor", "Trismus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Sleep disorder", "Enuresis", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Coprolalia", "Tetany", "Skin lesion", "Rumination"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Oliguria", "Male infertility", "Dark urine", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Uveitis", "Edema", "Anger", "Uveitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Urge incontinence", "Compulsive behavior", "Wandering", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Self-harm", "Orthopnea", "Delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Conjunctivitis", "Irritability", "Speech disorder", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Intrusive thoughts", "Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Flatulence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Nystagmus", "Dermatitis", "Fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Tinnitus", "Dizziness", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Bigger mole diameter", "Glabellar reflex", "Difficulty Focusing", "Hepatomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Pulmonary consolidation", "Froment's sign", "Lightheadedness", "Amenorrhoea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Laryngitis", "Stupor", "Bronchiectasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Tendonitis", "Middle back pain", "Shallow breathing", "Phonological deficit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Hematuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Chorea", "Toothache", "Guilt", "Blackout"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Leukocytosis", "Fatigue", "Urinary Frequency"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Emotional insecurity", "Wart", "Mouth breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Akathisia", "Compulsive hoarding", "Neck mass", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Paraphasia", "Sleep deprivation", "Petechia", "Hepatomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Fox's sign", "Biliary colic", "Cervical cancer", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Toe walking", "Tremor", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Cyanosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Myopathy", "Echolalia", "Cyanosis", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Crackles", "Shock", "Iron deficiency", "Diaphoresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Social isolation", "Diarrhea", "Ascites", "Quadriplegia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Colitis", "Compulsive hoarding", "Anterograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Goitre", "Abdominal mass", "Joint stiffness", "Feeling of impending doom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Racing thoughts", "Malar rash", "Abdominal mass", "Thyrotoxicosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Hyperventilation", "Thrombocytopenia", "Glossitis", "Pathological laughing and crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Watery diarrhea", "Bleeding diathesis", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety?", "answers": ["Hemoptysis", "Abdominal pain", "Keratitis", "Nocturnal Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Pericarditis", "Hypoxemia", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Bleeding gums", "Nervousness", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Otorrhea", "Weight loss", "Lymphocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Swelling", "Watery diarrhea", "Stunted growth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Hirsutism", "Chest pain", "Feeling of impending doom", "Rectal prolapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Echolalia", "Cramp", "Fever", "Amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Chancre", "Fatigue", "Impetigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Self-harm", "Tachypnea", "Night Sweats", "Anterograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Non-Hodgkin lymphoma?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Thought insertion", "Diabetes mellitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Anuria", "Nodule", "Watery diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Short stature", "Froment's sign", "Vesical tenesmus", "Bronchophony"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Hypomimia", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Fever", "Asterixis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Chills", "Pale feces", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Retching", "Bronchiectasis", "Polydipsia", "Balance disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Low-grade fever", "Watery diarrhea", "Petechia", "Muscle atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Seborrheic dermatitis", "Hypogonadism", "Astasia-abasia", "Bone fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Raynaud's phenomenon", "Asymptomatic", "Vision loss", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Rhonchi", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Renal failure", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Bruxism", "Emaciation", "Echolalia", "Periorbital puffiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Hemoptysis", "Excessive Crying", "Caput medusae"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Ventricular tachycardia", "Joint pain", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Fatigue", "Terry's nails", "Burning Chest Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Erythroplakia", "Chronic cough", "Leg pain", "Vertigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Anasarca", "Bone pain", "Cyst"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Flushing", "Fibrosis", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Bruxism", "Acute abdomen", "Joint effusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Erythema nodosum", "Forgetfulness", "Koilonychia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Pathological laughing and crying", "Vaginal discharge", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Skin tag"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Retching", "Ascites", "Bradykinesia", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Leukorrhea", "Cough", "Cyst", "Nephrotic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Rectal prolapse", "Dysmenorrhea", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Keratitis", "Depression", "Rovsing's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Wheals", "Synovitis", "Opportunistic infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Cold sensitivity", "Night Sweats", "Forgetfulness", "Hallucination"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tuberculosis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Intrusive thoughts", "Change in sexual interest", "Dysgeusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Fibromyalgia", "Compulsive behavior", "Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Wandering", "Hypervigilance", "Bruxism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Flashback", "Dacryoadenitis", "Apraxia", "Border irregularity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Acute bronchitis", "Eosinophilia", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Otorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Microalbuminuria", "Irritability", "Cardiac arrest", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Nightmare", "Hematospermia", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Posttraumatic stress disorder?", "answers": ["Pain behind the eyes", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Insomnia", "Cramp"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Blurred vision", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Sleep disturbances", "Radiculopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Risky behavior", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism", "Conjunctivitis", "Swollen tonsils"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Vascular Leak", "Skin rash", "Burning Chest Pain", "Water-electrolyte imbalance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Pus", "Tachylalia", "Quadriplegia", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Low-grade fever", "Ptosis", "Fibromyalgia", "Fox's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Bacterial vaginosis", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Photophobia", "Stunted growth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Stuttering", "Constipation", "Blister", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Pain", "Hematoma", "Acute abdomen", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Stiffness", "Bleeding", "Stomatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Guilt", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Psychosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Crepitus", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Facial nerve paralysis", "Vascular Leak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Iritis", "Red eye", "Astasia-abasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Fever", "Thrombosis", "Lightheadedness", "Globus pharyngis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Genital ulcer", "Headache", "Major depressive episode", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Mania", "Grandiose delusion", "Uveitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Dermatitis", "Male infertility", "Hutchinson's sign", "Acanthosis nigricans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Bacterial vaginosis", "Chronic pain", "Cyst", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Ataxia", "Loss of smell", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Weight loss", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Cloudy urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Keratitis", "Agnosia", "Blackout", "Fox's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Tophus", "Angina Pectoris", "Sore throat", "Bell's palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Convulsion", "Sadness", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Compulsive hoarding", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Mouth ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Erythema", "Facial pain", "Metabolic acidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Formication", "Colitis", "Hypertriglyceridemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Vaginal bleeding", "Necrosis", "Diarrhea", "Bone tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Wandering", "Numbness of face", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Barrel chest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Bronchospasm", "Pyuria", "Impulsivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Hepatic encephalopathy", "Malaise", "Bone Loss", "Risky behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Bruise", "Mental confusion", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes zoster?", "answers": ["Anhidrosis", "Chronic cough", "Muscle Spasms", "Paresthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Constipation?", "answers": ["Sleep disorder", "Pain", "Psychosis", "Labored breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Cloudy urine", "Hyperacusis", "Sexual obsessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Froment's sign", "Narrow stools", "Fatigue", "Air crescent sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Avolition", "Bruise", "Abdominal mass", "Slurred Speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Myoclonus", "Levine's sign", "Weight loss", "Lumbago"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Swollen testicle", "Fever", "Anhedonia", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Bruxism", "Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Pelvic pain", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Bone pain", "Avolition", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Allergic conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute myeloid leukemia?", "answers": ["Cough", "Immunodeficiency", "Infection", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Hepatomegaly", "Enuresis", "Chronic pain", "Candidiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Tendonitis", "Blurred vision", "Melancholia", "Leg pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Polydipsia", "Dystonia", "Hypersalivation", "Inverted nipple"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Proctitis", "Malnutrition", "Oligomenorrhea", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Tenderness", "Rebound tenderness", "Vomiting", "Balance disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Asymptomatic", "Malaise", "Uremia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Akathisia", "Lower motor neuron lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gestational diabetes?", "answers": ["Levine's sign", "Facial pain", "Nausea", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Vasoconstriction", "Low-grade fever", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Erectile dysfunction", "Hypertonia", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Stuttering", "Swollen feet", "Retching"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Hypersomnia", "Proteinuria", "Difficulty walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Hearing problem", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Foul smelling urine", "Dizziness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Grey Turner's sign", "Palpitation", "Renal failure", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Gingival enlargement", "Cervical cancer", "Panic attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Chills", "Dandruff", "Photosensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Hot flash", "Cardiac arrest", "Wandering", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Headache", "Uremia", "Chemosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Panic disorder?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Pharyngitis", "Diaphoresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Atrophy", "Blurred vision", "Monomelic amyotrophy", "Vaginal tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Fox's sign", "Slurred Speech", "Shock", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Carelessness", "Fatigue", "Erythroplakia", "Leukocytosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Anal swelling", "Bounding pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Carpal tunnel syndrome?", "answers": ["Chronic pain", "Hemolytic anemia", "Paresthesia", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Intestinal Obstruction?", "answers": ["Euphoria", "Suicidal ideation", "Halos around lights", "Abdominal distension"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dementia?", "answers": ["Astasia-abasia", "Chorea", "Vasculitis", "Medulloblastoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dementia?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Agitation", "Pruritus ani", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dementia?", "answers": ["Chest Tightness", "Paranoia", "Rose spots", "Delirium"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dementia?", "answers": ["Hyperkalemia", "Amnesia", "Blumberg sign", "Loss of interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dementia?", "answers": ["Personality or behavior changes", "Diabetes mellitus", "Erythema chronicum migrans", "Gingival enlargement"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dementia?", "answers": ["Hallucination", "Pain behind the eyes", "Vasculitis", "Chorea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Urethritis", "Costovertebral angle tenderness", "Agnosia", "Flatulence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Globus pharyngis", "Spasticity", "Lower motor neuron lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Trismus", "Nystagmus", "Hormonal disorders"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Night terror", "Anuria", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Terry's nails", "Hematoma", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Chills", "Vomiting", "Grandiose delusion", "Lipodystrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastritis?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Intestinal varices", "Eye pain", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Eczema", "Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Vesicle", "Enanthem"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Leukocytosis", "Hearing problem", "Hyperventilation", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Retrograde amnesia", "Failure to thrive", "Wandering"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Bradykinesia", "Hyperpigmentation", "Intertrigo", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Dysuria", "Chronic cough", "Somnolence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Muscle Spasms", "Nuchal Rigidity", "Periorbital puffiness", "Carpal tunnel syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Ecchymosis", "Hiccup", "Pica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Numbness of the face or tongue", "Swelling", "Bronchophony", "Asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Hydrocele", "Dry Eye", "Aphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Obesity", "Genital sores", "Delayed reading ability", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Medulloblastoma", "Tonsillitis", "Hyperthermia", "Gait abnormality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Hirano body", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Abscess", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Hepatosplenomegaly", "Pruritus ani", "Groin Lump", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Disinhibition", "Sore throat", "Proteinuria", "Psychosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Lack of Remorse", "Tachycardia", "Change in bowel habits", "Halitosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Night Sweats", "Photopsia", "Hyperesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Chills", "Hematemesis", "Keratitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Rhonchi", "Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Barrel chest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Metabolic acidosis", "Nipple tenderness", "Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Raynaud's phenomenon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Ileus", "Muscle Spasms", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Facial nerve paralysis", "Pancreatitis", "Thrombocytopenia", "Social isolation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Stereotypy", "Blood in stool", "Knee pain", "Skin rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Markle sign", "Dyskinesia", "Malaise", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Abdominal distension", "Lethargy", "Polydipsia", "Dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Difficulty walking", "Headache", "Opportunistic infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "Sleep deprivation", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Sleep apnea", "Jaundice", "Intermittent claudication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Quadriplegia", "Irregular menstruation", "Tachypnea", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Photophobia", "Cervical cancer", "Cloudy urine", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Erythroplakia", "Back pain", "Amenorrhoea", "Rose spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Depression", "Cervical cancer", "Collapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Glabellar reflex", "Peripheral edema", "Kehr's sign", "Bone tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Apraxia", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Hepatomegaly", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Dacryoadenitis", "Change in bowel habits", "Hyperglycemia", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Abdominal pain", "Otalgia", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Petechia", "Anuria", "Abdominal distension", "Optic neuritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Splenomegaly", "Mastodynia", "Rheumatoid nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Nervousness", "Lymphocytosis", "Trismus", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Leg pain", "Ketoacidosis", "Costovertebral angle tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Vasoconstriction", "Opisthotonus", "Erythroplakia", "Tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Wheals", "Nosebleed", "Intrusive thoughts", "Dysarthria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Infectious mononucleosis?", "answers": ["Hives", "Photopsia", "Dyspareunia", "Rectal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Sexual obsessions", "Hydrocele", "Blister"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Pus", "Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Urinary urgency", "Levine's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Rhonchi", "Drooling", "Insomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Ketoacidosis", "Diarrhea", "Risus sardonicus", "Flushing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Amenorrhoea", "Leukorrhea", "Sleep disturbances", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Loss Of Consciousness", "Guilt", "Horner's syndrome", "Skin rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Ventricular tachycardia", "Swollen legs", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Urinary tract infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Hyperactivity", "Bone pain", "Nikolsky's sign", "Lack of Concentration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Muehrcke's nails", "Optic neuritis", "Pain", "Petechia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Furuncle", "Dyskinesia", "Necrosis", "Stuttering"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Enthesitis", "Trismus", "Desquamation", "Stupor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Tic", "Kussmaul's sign", "/m/0lxt", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Dysphonia", "Cyst", "Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Apraxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Abdominal mass", "Arthritis", "Itchy eyes", "Bubo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Gingival recession", "Hypothermia", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Nervousness", "Chills", "Malar rash", "Snoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Staphylococcal infection?", "answers": ["Vaginal discharge", "Dysesthesia", "Abscess", "Hearing problem"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Acute bronchitis", "Intestinal varices", "Hydrocele", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Quadriplegia", "Retrograde amnesia", "Lumbago", "Dark urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Toe walking", "Myerson's sign", "Neck pain", "Painless testicular lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Hematospermia", "Hyperkeratosis", "Leukorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Stuttering", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Swollen testicle", "Leukocytosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Testicular cancer?", "answers": ["Sexual dysfunction", "Dissociative disorder", "Skin rash", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Hypertension", "Angina Pectoris", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Mania", "Ecchymosis", "Malaise", "Chorioretinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Vertigo", "Intertrigo", "Avolition", "Stomatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Stereotypy", "Phonophobia", "Verbosity", "Conductive hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Sexual dysfunction", "Weight loss", "Vasculitis", "Flushing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Sore throat", "Arthritis", "Dieting"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Psychosis", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Watery diarrhea", "Pus", "Low-grade fever", "Inverted nipple"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Dehydration", "Wart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Morphea", "Pallor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Mental illness", "Balance disorder", "Red eye", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis?", "answers": ["Major depression", "Cyanosis", "Nosebleed", "Tinnitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Sleep disturbances", "Astasia-abasia", "Wheals"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Failure to thrive", "Body ache", "Hematemesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Telangiectasia", "Enanthem", "Hyperactivity", "Restless legs syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Border irregularity", "Choreoathetosis", "Eructation", "Extreme Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Fetor hepaticus", "Nodule", "Bone tumor", "Indigestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Skin lesion", "Hyperlipidemia", "Phyllodes tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Skin cancer?", "answers": ["Carelessness", "Melanocytic nevus", "Scotoma", "Otalgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tear of meniscus?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Red eye", "Cyanosis", "Orofacial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tear of meniscus?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Mastodynia", "Knee pain", "Chorioretinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Sleep disturbances", "Thought disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Tinnitus", "Wheeze", "Loose teeth", "Lack of empathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Hypersomnia", "Pursed lip breathing", "Phonophobia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Barrel chest", "Erythema multiforme", "Hyperhidrosis", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Change in sexual interest", "Intellectual disability", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Thought insertion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Cyanosis", "Pallor", "Erythema chronicum migrans", "Periorbital puffiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Difficulty walking", "Lack of empathy", "Sputum", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Tachypnea", "Bounding pulse", "Vasoconstriction", "Maculopapular rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Panic attack", "Constipation", "Asterixis", "Lower motor neuron lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease?", "answers": ["Erectile dysfunction", "Goitre", "Nausea", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sexually transmitted disease?", "answers": ["Hypoxemia", "Phlegm", "Jaundice", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Flashback", "Horner's syndrome", "Kaposi's sarcoma", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Intrusive thoughts", "Xerostomia", "Cachexia", "Agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Muehrcke's nails", "Fibromyalgia", "Photopsia", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Balance disorder", "Hypersomnia", "Emotional insecurity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Delirium", "Costovertebral angle tenderness", "Diaphoresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Body ache", "Myopathy", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Excessive daytime sleepiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Lhermitte's sign", "Heart murmur"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Dysmenorrhea", "Eosinophilia", "Conjunctivitis", "Snoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obstructive sleep apnea?", "answers": ["Coagulopathy", "Emotional insecurity", "Sore throat", "Desquamation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Clonus", "Erythema", "Anal fissure", "Muscle atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Sundowning", "Bladder spasm", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Sleep disturbances", "Bleeding", "Orthopnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Scaly skin", "Hypocalcaemia", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Azotemia", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Blister", "Cold sensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Papule", "Gait abnormality", "Bone fracture", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Dandruff", "Burning Chest Pain", "Narrow stools"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Hyperpigmentation", "Deafness", "/m/0lxt", "Urinary Frequency"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ringworm?", "answers": ["Hypertonia", "Stomatitis", "Genital sores", "Alopecia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Anxiety", "Mouth breathing", "Pressure of speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Watery eyes", "Avoidant personality disorder", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Dissociative disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Fox's sign", "Lethargy", "Intrusive thoughts", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Racing thoughts", "Leukorrhea", "Genital wart", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Tic", "Dyschezia", "Ascites", "Increased vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Goitre", "Dizziness", "Pressure of speech", "Social isolation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Fox's sign", "Swollen testicle", "Hyperkeratosis", "Palilalia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Myelopathy", "Alopecia", "Menorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Breast lump", "Compulsive hoarding", "Cracked Skin", "Anasarca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Pathological laughing and crying", "Blister", "Pressure of speech", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Bruise", "Purpura", "Change in bowel habits", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Paget's disease of the breast", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Chorea", "Aggression", "Coprolalia", "Increased vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Obsessive-compulsive disorder?", "answers": ["Wart", "Sexual obsessions", "Rhinitis", "Mole color changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Psoriatic arthritis?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Allergic conjunctivitis", "Photopsia", "Dactylitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Psoriatic arthritis?", "answers": ["Renal colic", "Vascular Leak", "Malar rash", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Psoriatic arthritis?", "answers": ["Candidiasis", "Tendonitis", "Hyperkeratosis", "Fourth heart sound"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Coronary artery disease?", "answers": ["Crackles", "Asterixis", "Chorea", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Coronary artery disease?", "answers": ["High Fever", "Intertrigo", "Cardiac arrest", "Cullen's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Concussion?", "answers": ["Agnosia", "Impulsivity", "Fetor hepaticus", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Iritis", "Tic", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Emotional insecurity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Fever", "Sensorineural hearing loss", "Bleeding on probing", "Stuttering"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Stupor", "Mental confusion", "Low-grade fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Markle sign", "Oral bleeding", "Collapse", "Speech delay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Watery eyes", "Itchy eyes", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Sexual dysfunction", "Medulloblastoma", "Delayed reading ability", "Rumination"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Caput medusae", "Anal fissure", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dyslexia?", "answers": ["Ecchymosis", "Dactylitis", "Phyllodes tumor", "Phonological deficit"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Melanoma?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Nasal congestion", "Restricted behavior", "Mole color changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Melanoma?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Ageusia", "Deafness", "Border irregularity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Melanoma?", "answers": ["Lethargy", "Pain", "Watery diarrhea", "Loose teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Melanoma?", "answers": ["Retching", "Bigger mole diameter", "Loss of smell", "Xerostomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Melanoma?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Fibrosis", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Melanoma?", "answers": ["Air crescent sign", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Asymmetry", "Fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Impetigo", "Numbness of the face or tongue", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Myerson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Photosensitivity", "Malnutrition", "Eye pain", "Agitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Facial nerve paralysis", "Necrosis", "Lethargy", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Chorioretinitis", "Ventricular tachycardia", "Slurred Speech", "Runny nose"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Brittle nails", "Cullen's sign", "Neck mass", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Vascular Leak", "Substance abuse", "Skin lesion", "Gait abnormality"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Swollen testicle", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Abscess", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Tree-in-bud sign", "Diplopia", "Fever", "Agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Phlebitis", "Leukocytosis", "Vertigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Thrombosis", "Itchy eyes", "Muscle weakness", "Sneeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Transient ischemic attack?", "answers": ["Synovitis", "Morphea", "Sleep disorder", "Vision loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Migraine?", "answers": ["Urinary incontinence", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Vasoconstriction", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Retrograde amnesia", "Glossitis", "Cough", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Swollen feet", "Carpal tunnel syndrome", "Sinusitis", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Cervical cancer", "Dementia", "Steatorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Bleeding on probing", "Skin rash", "Change in bowel habits", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Chest Tightness", "Hiccup", "Toothache", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Dysosmia", "Abdominal pain", "Sexual obsessions", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Nosebleed", "Penile discharge", "Allergic conjunctivitis", "Hepatorenal syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Dyschezia", "Fecal incontinence", "Bloating", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Leukopenia", "Dyspnea", "Cardiac asthma", "Psoas sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Pelvic pain", "Asthma", "Impulsivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Rhinitis", "Chest pain", "Necrosis", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Tremor", "Sneeze", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Allergy?", "answers": ["Wheals", "Body ache", "Loss of smell", "Dysuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Dysosmia", "Enanthem", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Hives", "Nervousness", "Swelling", "Central facial palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Hypomania", "Skin rash", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Retching", "Erythema", "Leukocytosis", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Water retention", "Headache", "Aphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Psoas sign", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Speech delay", "Anal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Fibromyalgia", "Paresthesia", "Hyperreflexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Tetany", "Numbness of the face or tongue", "Proctitis", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Immunodeficiency", "Laryngitis", "Chills", "Hives"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Inflammation", "Meningitis", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Hematoma", "Genital sores", "Bunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Orthostatic hypotension", "Gait abnormality", "Auditory hallucination", "Skin ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Vaginal discharge", "Phonophobia", "Chronic cough", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Ptosis", "Stroke", "Hives"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Hyperkalemia", "Flatulence", "Urinary incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Gingivitis", "Blister", "Steatorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Ataxia", "Dysuria", "Panic attack", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Phonophobia", "Dysesthesia", "Fever", "Abdominal distension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Genital ulcer", "Social isolation", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Atrophy", "Pain", "Ptosis", "Koilonychia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Obesity", "Urinary retention", "Penile discharge", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Knee pain", "Mental confusion", "Parkinsonism", "Narrow stools"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Leg pain", "Swollen tonsils", "Vaginal bleeding", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Pruritus", "Myopathy", "Abdominal obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Asymptomatic", "Osteoporosis", "Gait abnormality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Brittle nails", "Muscle pain", "Cramp", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Bone Loss", "Hyperesthesia", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Genital herpes?", "answers": ["Neck mass", "Glabellar reflex", "Cervicitis", "Compulsive hoarding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Spasticity", "Melancholia", "Hypersexuality", "Xerostomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "Hemiplegia", "Vaginal dryness", "Left ventricular hypertrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Eosinophilia", "Dehydration", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Internal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Astasia-abasia", "Fourth heart sound", "Hyperventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Eosinophilia", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Gynecomastia", "Paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Urinary retention", "Bone tumor", "Hematuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Colitis", "Pruritus", "Nightmare", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Impulsivity", "Obturator sign", "Arthritis", "Markle sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Neuralgia", "Odynophagia", "Muscle pain", "Medulloblastoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Rhinitis", "Leukopenia", "Swollen legs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Retching", "Uveitis", "Muehrcke's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Photophobia", "Dyskinesia", "Fever", "Xerophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Stiffness", "Chills", "Mania", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Delirium", "Hearing problem", "Hyperventilation", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Slurred Speech", "Rectal tenesmus", "Renal failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Diarrhea", "Dry Eye", "Delayed milestone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Failure to thrive", "Chorea", "Nausea", "Vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Rumination", "Hives", "Lymphocytopenia", "Kussmaul's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Lightheadedness", "Bigger mole diameter", "Xerophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Diplopia", "Difficulty Focusing", "Skin Discoloration", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Photophobia", "Dizziness", "Neuralgia", "Substance-related disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Dacryoadenitis", "Joint effusion", "Vomiting", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Loss of smell", "Aphasia", "Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Photosensitivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Toe walking", "Angular cheilitis", "Obturator sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Horner's syndrome", "Hypothermia", "Oligomenorrhea", "Hematemesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Hypoxemia", "Racing thoughts", "Indigestion", "Postural instability"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Pelvic pain", "Fatigue", "Vaginal discharge", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Dysphagia", "Desquamation", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Flushing", "Facial pain", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Orthostatic hypotension", "Headache", "Major depressive episode", "Vasculitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Delayed milestone", "Irregular menstruation", "Malaise", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Back pain", "Pancreatitis", "Speech delay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Food poisoning?", "answers": ["Breast lump", "Gingival recession", "Suicidal ideation", "Blood in stool"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Nikolsky's sign", "Globus pharyngis", "Breakthrough bleeding", "Allergic conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Myocardial infarction", "Tunnel vision", "Impetigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Nipple discharge", "Chest pain", "Itchy eyes", "Dizziness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Indigestion", "Mania", "Flashback"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Tachypnea", "Oral bleeding", "Pyuria", "Dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Stiff neck", "Pain", "Crepitus", "Self-harm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Phlebitis", "Psychomotor retardation", "Abdominal pain", "Wart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Palpitation", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Brittle nails", "Nausea", "Rectal prolapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Retching", "Acute bronchitis", "Genital ulcer", "Dandruff"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Syncope", "Tonsillitis", "Tumor", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Stridor", "Odynophagia", "Tophus", "Hypersalivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Increased vaginal discharge", "Myocardial infarction", "Goitre", "Heartburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Peripheral edema", "Swollen testicle", "Rectal prolapse", "Hematemesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Pyuria", "Lipodystrophy", "Nipple tenderness", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Monomelic amyotrophy", "Hiccup", "Heberden's node", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Otalgia", "Pathological laughing and crying", "Horner's syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hiatal hernia?", "answers": ["Compulsive behavior", "Eosinophilia", "Asymptomatic", "High Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Anxiety", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Hypoglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Shock", "Petechia", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Hypomimia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Infection", "Facial pain", "Dermatitis", "Fibrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Weight gain", "Tremor", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Night Sweats"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Stiffness", "Cervical cancer", "Dactylitis", "Lymphocytosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Anal swelling", "Hypoxia", "Dehydration", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Fetor hepaticus", "Cervical cancer", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Barrel chest", "Bradypnea", "Bone pain", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Leukoplakia", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Hepatomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Dermatitis", "Muscle weakness", "Thrombosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Astasia-abasia", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Nephritic syndrome", "Homicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Paralysis", "Anterograde amnesia", "Pericarditis", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Anuria", "Constipation", "Anhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Bleeding", "Bronchiectasis", "Tendonitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Bleeding diathesis", "Glossodynia", "Skin Discoloration", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Postural instability", "Gingival enlargement", "Bigger mole diameter", "Synovitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Painless testicular lump", "Narcissism", "Nausea", "Toothache"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Polyphagia", "Cyst"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Asymmetry", "Myocardial infarction", "Bleeding on probing", "Obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Leukemia?", "answers": ["Melena", "Body ache", "Pruritus", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Enuresis", "Thrombocytopenia", "Heart failure", "Oligomenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Tonsillitis", "Cardiac asthma", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Myelopathy", "Hemoperitoneum", "Emotional insecurity", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Urinary tract infection", "Hutchinson's sign", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Tachypnea", "Sore throat", "Sadness", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Skin Discoloration", "Gingival recession", "Painless testicular lump", "Genital wart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sepsis?", "answers": ["Bradypnea", "Myoclonus", "Fever", "Stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Change in bowel habits", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine", "Xerophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Leg pain", "Inflammation", "Hypersomnia", "Leukorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Fetor hepaticus", "Menorrhagia", "Cardiac arrest", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Micrographia", "Bradycardia", "Excessive Crying", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Dark urine", "Painful ejaculation", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Synovitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Hepatomegaly", "Pulmonary hypertension", "Pharyngitis", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Clouding of consciousness", "Ageusia", "Jaundice", "Erythema nodosum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Fox's sign", "Uveitis", "Blister", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Nystagmus", "Delusion", "Anal swelling", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Pale feces", "Vertigo", "Nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Polyneuropathy", "Nasal congestion", "Edema", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Somnolence", "Nocturia", "Syncope", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Compulsive hoarding", "Spasticity", "Spider angioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Glossitis", "Scotoma", "Painful ejaculation", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Microalbuminuria", "Pelvic pain", "Hot flash", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Hypokinesia", "Anorexia", "Dysmenorrhea", "Lhermitte's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Fever", "Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Heberden's node", "Hyperventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Chorioretinitis", "Dissociative disorder", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis B?", "answers": ["Stunted growth", "Ageusia", "Asymptomatic", "Bell's palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Dermatitis", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Vaginitis", "Acalculia", "Tumor", "Stridor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Crackles", "Dysarthria", "Bubo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Maculopapular rash", "Lymphocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Chorioretinitis", "Toothache", "Delirium", "Lactose intolerance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Pallor", "Seizure", "Photosensitivity", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Muscle atrophy", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Bronchophony"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Muscle weakness", "Cyanosis", "Spasticity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Nasal congestion", "Delayed puberty", "Diaphoresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Scotoma", "Rectal prolapse", "Proctitis", "Joint effusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Tetany", "Ketoacidosis", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Hypokinesia", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Hives"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Cachexia", "Hydrocele", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Dysosmia", "Hirsutism", "Alopecia", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Vertigo", "Hypokinesia", "Tophus", "Intermittent claudication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Spinal tumor", "Deformity", "Lack of Remorse", "Hyperglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Nervousness", "Anal fissure", "Diplopia", "Stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Intrusive thoughts", "Urethritis", "Nerve injury", "Synovitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Cerebellar ataxia", "Pneumonia", "Anxiety", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Watery diarrhea", "Bone tumor", "Stroke", "Substance-related disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Type 2 diabetes", "Frequent urination", "Homicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Palilalia", "Arthropathy", "Bloating", "Shallow breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Papule", "Emotional insecurity", "Racing thoughts", "Nasal polyp"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Abdominal obesity", "Renal failure", "Nightmare", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Hypersomnia", "Skin rash", "Phonological deficit", "Stiff neck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Lack of empathy", "Abdominal pain", "Azotemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Pus", "Dark urine", "Anterograde amnesia", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Carelessness", "Lymphocytosis", "Myopathy", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Glossitis", "Short stature", "Shivering", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Coprolalia", "Glossodynia", "Pain", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Pancreatitis", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Difficulty Focusing", "Extreme Weight Loss", "Abscess"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Dyskinesia", "Mania", "Risus sardonicus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Bleeding gums", "Eczema", "Fever", "Inferiority complex"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Dermatitis", "Post-void dribbling", "Neuralgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Blank Stare", "Glycosuria", "Genital ulcer", "Pleuritic chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Angina Pectoris", "Uveitis", "Major depressive episode", "Obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Myxedema", "Neuralgia", "Cardiac asthma", "Chancre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Syphilis?", "answers": ["Eosinophilia", "Nodule", "Tachypnea", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Visual verbal agnosia", "Vision disorder", "Coprolalia", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Phlegm", "Dry cough", "Personality or behavior changes", "Hypersomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Cyst", "Convulsion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Major depressive episode", "Eructation", "Painless testicular lump", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Gingival enlargement", "Pain", "Chills"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Difficulty Focusing", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Polydipsia", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Pressure of speech", "Insomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Feeling of impending doom", "Stupor", "Asymptomatic", "Papule"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Cachexia", "Sadness", "Rectal tenesmus", "Rovsing's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Glabellar reflex", "Mood swing", "Failure to thrive", "Erythroplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Fasciculation", "Hemoptysis", "Palmar erythema", "Anhedonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Iritis", "Water retention", "Internal bleeding", "Aggression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Vesical tenesmus", "Boredom", "Post-void dribbling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Knee pain", "Rectal bleeding", "Nightmare", "Biliary colic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["cerebella tumor", "Fetor hepaticus", "Anger", "Cervical lymphadenopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Papule", "Inferiority complex", "Catatonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Anasarca", "Tic", "Impulsivity", "Intrusive thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Muscle atrophy", "Dysesthesia", "Guilt", "Mouth breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Oliguria", "Dysphoria", "Phyllodes tumor", "Froment's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Rectal pain", "Rumination", "Retching", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Neck mass", "Papule", "Major depressive episode", "Self-harm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Irritability", "Enophthalmia", "Cotton wool spots", "Sleep disturbances"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Depression?", "answers": ["Bell's palsy", "Anxiety", "Cirrhosis", "Groin Lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Laryngitis", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Heart murmur"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Thyroid nodule", "Halitosis", "Narcissism", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Kussmaul's sign", "Dysphonia", "Facial swelling", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Neck pain", "Hemolytic anemia", "Hyperkalemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Oligomenorrhea", "Chronic cough", "Phyllodes tumor", "Dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Tremor", "Wart", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Sore throat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Thyroid cancer?", "answers": ["Phlebitis", "Dyspnea", "Leukoplakia", "Nephritic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rotator cuff tear?", "answers": ["Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Halitosis", "Stiffness", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rotator cuff tear?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Laryngitis", "Watery eyes", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rotator cuff tear?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Splenomegaly", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Bruise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Cloudy urine", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Bounding pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Increased vaginal discharge", "Hematoma", "Nausea", "Skin rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute pancreatitis?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Odynophagia", "Coagulopathy", "Fox's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Pericarditis", "Vision disorder", "Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Urinary incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Angina Pectoris", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Facial swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Difficulty walking", "Compulsive behavior", "Tonsillitis", "Mania"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Bunion", "Hyperlipidemia", "Bell's palsy", "Muscle weakness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Retrograde amnesia", "Malnutrition", "Sweating", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Syncope", "Rectal bleeding", "Hiccup", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vertigo?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Major depressive episode", "Vomiting", "Vaginal tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Labored breathing", "Bone tumor", "Nystagmus", "Vision disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Obturator sign", "Photopsia", "Frequent urination", "Avolition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Urinary Frequency", "Lumbago", "Photophobia", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Hemiparesis", "Bouchard's nodes", "Vision loss", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Hypercapnia", "Amnesia", "Tunnel vision", "Acne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Malnutrition", "Gynecomastia", "Floater", "Hypoglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Deformity", "Splenomegaly", "Scotoma", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Numbness", "Anorexia", "Blurred vision", "Palilalia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Retinal detachment?", "answers": ["Irritability", "Portal hypertension", "Sleep deprivation", "Diplopia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Cotton wool spots", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Dementia", "Low-grade fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Blank Stare", "Flashback", "Nosebleed", "Rheumatoid nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Blurred vision", "Urinary urgency", "Hypoxemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Stridor", "Pulmonary edema", "Anger", "Spasticity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Emaciation", "Intertrigo", "Palmar erythema"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Barrel chest", "Compulsive behavior", "Dacryoadenitis", "Bounding pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Scotoma", "Fatigue", "Crepitus", "Postural instability"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Hyperglycemia", "Aggression", "Dizziness", "Hyperpigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Tachylalia", "Osler's sign", "Bruxism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Fourth heart sound", "Mental confusion", "Papule"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Halitosis", "Vomiting", "Clouding of consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Gait abnormality", "Fourth heart sound", "Headache", "Pain behind the eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Air crescent sign", "Dyspnea", "Watery diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Inferiority complex", "Blepharospasm", "Vision disorder", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Wandering", "Somnolence", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Anal fissure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Thought insertion", "Loss Of Consciousness", "Hunger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Pyuria", "Irregular menstruation", "Globus pharyngis", "Tinnitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Chorea", "Xerophthalmia", "Ecchymosis", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Pain", "Ataxia", "Alopecia", "Intertrigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Micrographia", "Agitation", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Trismus", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Oligomenorrhea", "Stupor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Fibrosis", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Froment's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Substance-related disorder", "Chills", "Proteinuria", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypertension?", "answers": ["Erectile dysfunction", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Diplopia", "Excessive Crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Glossitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Paget's disease of the breast", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Pallor", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Cachexia", "Stereotypy", "Joint pain", "Morphea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Iritis", "Meningism", "Skin rash", "Restless legs syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Vomiting", "Convulsion", "Convulsion", "Froment's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Inferiority complex", "Wheeze", "Blood in stool", "Substance abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Obesity", "Rose spots", "Papule"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Pancolitis", "Self-destructive behaviour", "Costovertebral angle tenderness", "Iron deficiency"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Flatulence", "Breast lump", "Conductive hearing loss", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Nail clubbing", "Abscess", "Spider angioma", "Dissociative disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ulcerative colitis?", "answers": ["Horner's syndrome", "Emotional insecurity", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Abnormal vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Bell's palsy", "Halos around lights", "Erythema chronicum migrans", "Goitre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Leg pain", "Depression", "Stiff neck", "Hypersomnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Azotemia", "Phlegm", "Atrophy", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Lack of empathy", "Polydipsia", "High Fever", "Increased vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Ascites", "Insomnia", "Vaginal tenderness", "Nephritic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Hematoma", "Anasarca", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Nervousness", "Pneumonia", "Quadriplegia", "Fetor hepaticus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Dyschezia", "Malocclusion", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Nasal polyp", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Delusion", "Cervical lymphadenopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Hepatomegaly", "Change in sexual interest", "Self-destructive behaviour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Phyllodes tumor", "Alopecia", "Risky behavior", "Bleeding diathesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Hemiplegia", "Muehrcke's nails", "Weight loss", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Urethritis", "Hallucination", "Eye pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Markle sign", "Otorrhea", "Petechia", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Desquamation", "Chorea", "Orthostatic hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Vomiting", "Clonus", "Toe walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Personality or behavior changes", "Lymphocytopenia", "Hemiplegia", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Muehrcke's nails", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Tachycardia", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Bunion", "Glossodynia", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Increased vaginal discharge", "Polyuria", "Blumberg sign", "Bradypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hyperthyroidism?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Hypokinesia", "Meningism", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Decreased level of consciousness", "Watery eyes", "Anhedonia", "Paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Loss of interest", "Abdominal pain", "Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Pharyngitis", "Vesicle", "Cullen's sign", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Paresthesia", "Kaposi's sarcoma", "Slurred Speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Weight gain", "Nasal congestion", "Photosensitivity", "Hypervigilance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Sinusitis", "Weight loss", "Hypervigilance", "Bradycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Abdominal obesity", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Major depression", "Agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Phonophobia", "Iron deficiency", "Body ache", "Nail clubbing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine", "Delayed reading ability", "Anorexia", "Micrographia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Hiccup", "Red eye", "Gingivitis", "Nocturia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Menorrhagia", "Blood in stool", "Tendonitis", "Chills"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Terry's nails", "Diaphoresis", "Photosensitivity", "Swollen tonsils"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Cachexia", "Itchy eyes", "Burning Chest Pain", "Flushing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Cullen's sign", "Acute abdomen", "Malaise", "Sadness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Thrombocytopenia", "Vision disorder", "Headache", "Ascites"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Golden S sign", "Oligomenorrhea", "Muscle weakness", "Ventricular tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Wandering", "Hemoptysis", "Kaposi's sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Heart murmur", "Malocclusion", "Constipation", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Echolalia", "Bell's palsy", "Oligomenorrhea", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Shivering", "Photopsia", "Internal bleeding", "Fourth heart sound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Delirium", "Pain", "Hypersalivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Influenza?", "answers": ["Hepatosplenomegaly", "Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Cyanosis", "Blumberg sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Syncope", "Micrographia", "Rose spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Vomiting", "Dysphonia", "Hot flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Arthritis", "High Fever", "Dysuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Pallor", "Paresthesia", "Anasarca", "Primarily Obsessional OCD"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Dysphonia", "Hemoperitoneum", "Guilt", "Stiff neck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Hegar's sign", "Nipple tenderness", "Pressure of speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Hematospermia", "Leukoplakia", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Phlebitis", "Leukorrhea", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Infection", "Metrorrhagia", "Asthma", "Anhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Dyschezia", "Abdominal pain", "Joint effusion", "Disinhibition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Hypoxemia", "Vesicle", "Obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ectopic pregnancy?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Lightheadedness", "Clouding of consciousness", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Euphoria", "Heart murmur", "Schizophasia", "Malar rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Tachylalia", "Meningism", "Joint effusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Chest Tightness", "Vaginal odor", "Agitation", "Foul smelling urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Sadness", "Labored breathing", "Stereotypy", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Obesity", "Edema", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Polyphagia", "Lhermitte's sign", "Synovitis", "Stunted growth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Coagulopathy", "Hypomania", "Dissociative disorder", "Persistent urge to urinate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Urge incontinence", "Xerostomia", "Hypervigilance", "Hallucination"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Pulmonary edema", "Wart", "Pain", "Hyperhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Retrograde amnesia", "Bigger mole diameter", "Otorrhea", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Leukoplakia", "Opportunistic infection", "Pulmonary hypertension", "Racing thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Ptosis", "Slurred Speech", "Irritability", "Paraphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Guilt", "Cullen's sign", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Depression", "Tonsillitis", "Dysarthria", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Pancreatitis", "Intestinal varices", "Anhedonia", "Dandruff"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Nerve injury", "Impulsivity", "Ritualistic behavior", "Granuloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Aggression", "Nosebleed", "Swollen feet", "Conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Pruritus ani", "Flashback", "Upper respiratory tract infection", "Thought disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Pulsus paradoxus", "Impetigo", "Anasarca", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Nephritic syndrome", "Conjunctivitis", "Nightmare", "Heartburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Bone fracture", "Delusion", "Encephalopathy", "Type 2 diabetes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Risky behavior", "Numbness of face", "Hypogonadism", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Mania", "Hyperaemia", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Dysphonia", "Hyperactivity", "Psychomotor retardation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Erythroleukoplakia", "Enanthem", "Sore throat", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Nervousness", "Audible pop at time of injury", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Grandiose delusion", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Erythema nodosum", "Akathisia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Frontal release sign", "Hypoesthesia", "Hypersexuality", "Parkinsonism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Leukorrhea", "Erectile dysfunction", "Bubo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Mouth breathing", "Breast lump", "Loss of interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Failure to thrive", "Anxiety", "Anal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Hepatorenal syndrome", "Major depressive episode", "Tunnel vision", "Oliguria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Gingivitis", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Hematochezia", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Swollen feet", "Weight loss", "Muehrcke's nails", "Hypercapnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Sleep disturbances", "Anorexia", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Sleep deprivation", "Parkinsonism", "Syncope", "Vision loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Hypersomnia", "Sinusitis", "Lymphocytopenia", "Papule"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Hypervigilance", "Mood swing", "Odynophagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bipolar disorder?", "answers": ["Pressure of speech", "Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Hemiparesis", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Intrusive thoughts", "Acute bronchitis", "Postural instability", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Cold sensitivity", "Bell's palsy", "Frequent urination", "Nail clubbing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Portal hypertension", "Delayed puberty", "Rectal tenesmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Amnesia", "Cyanosis", "Speech delay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Enuresis", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Pretibial myxedema", "Self-destructive behaviour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Dieting", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Cracked Skin", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Pleuritic chest pain", "Opportunistic infection", "Lightheadedness", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Breast lump", "Back pain", "Dry cough", "Lethargy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Uveitis", "Fever", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Nuchal Rigidity", "Headache", "Cold sensitivity", "Vision loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Chills", "Night terror", "Hematochezia", "Thyrotoxicosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Hypogonadism", "Wandering", "Morphea", "Chorea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Fecal incontinence", "Nausea", "Thought disorder", "Swollen tonsils"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Erythema nodosum", "Frequent urination", "Muscle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Somnolence", "Post-nasal drip", "Obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Maculopapular rash", "Vasculitis", "Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Hearing problem", "Swollen tonsils", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Enanthem"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Erythema", "Quadriplegia", "High Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Hyperphosphatemia", "Bigger mole diameter", "Leukopenia", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Albuminuria", "Rhinitis", "Blurred vision", "Hyperkalemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Photopsia", "Vomiting", "Dermatitis", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Acanthosis nigricans", "Hypoxemia", "Formication", "Gynecomastia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Nuchal Rigidity", "Nasal congestion", "Hallucination", "Metrorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Audible pop at time of injury", "Hypoesthesia", "Dysphonia", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Dandruff", "Brittle nails", "Pharyngitis", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Genital sores", "Agnosia", "Alopecia", "Delayed onset muscle soreness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Hormonal disorders", "Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Facial nerve paralysis", "Trismus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Infection", "Crepitus", "Polyneuropathy", "Parosmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Hemolytic anemia", "Conductive hearing loss", "Inflammation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Metrorrhagia", "Malocclusion", "Cachexia", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Angina Pectoris", "Pain", "Substance abuse", "Skin lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Meningitis", "Pallor", "Toothache", "Gynecomastia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Gingival recession", "Proctitis", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Deformity", "Parkinsonism", "Erythema chronicum migrans", "Frontal release sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Atrophy", "Chest pain", "Malnutrition", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Cachexia", "Vaginal odor", "Auditory hallucination", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Bounding pulse", "Major depressive episode", "Pruritus", "Mouth breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Numbness", "Sleep disorder", "Lymphocytopenia", "Major depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Sore throat", "Snoring", "Postural instability"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Eosinophilia", "Cloudy urine", "Telangiectasia", "Dizziness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Vaginal dryness", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Paresthesia", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Vital Exhaustion", "Parkinsonism", "Halitosis", "Night Sweats"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Bleeding gums", "Change in bowel habits", "Photophobia", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Pulsus paradoxus", "Radiculopathy", "Abdominal mass", "Fatty liver"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Collapse", "Bradycardia", "Breast lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Groin Lump", "Wheeze", "Diplopia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Psychomotor retardation", "Crackles", "Syncope", "Rectal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Racing thoughts", "Tinnitus", "Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Erythroleukoplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Cyst", "Runny nose", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Boredom", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Bleeding on probing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lyme disease?", "answers": ["Excessive Crying", "Homicidal ideation", "Nipple tenderness", "Stiff neck"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cancer?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Thrombocytopenia", "cerebella tumor", "Dyskinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cancer?", "answers": ["Tree-in-bud sign", "Medulloblastoma", "Swollen testicle", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Ketoacidosis", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Irregular menstruation", "Aggression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Opisthotonus", "Change in sexual interest", "Hemiplegia", "Pseudologia fantastica"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Angina Pectoris", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Cerebellar ataxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Morphea", "Scaly skin", "Lack of Remorse", "Erythema multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Substance-related disorder", "Polyneuropathy", "Breast lump", "High Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Esophageal varices", "Narcissism", "Xeroderma", "Dehydration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Drooling", "Clonus", "Lack of empathy", "Rectal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Hemoperitoneum", "Impulsivity", "Anhedonia", "Central facial palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Dysphoria", "Markle sign", "Flu-like syndrome", "Glycosuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Antisocial personality disorder?", "answers": ["Paranoia", "Phlegm", "Cachexia", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Dystonia", "Halitosis", "Abdominal pain", "Bronchiectasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Breast lump", "Drooling", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Opportunistic infection", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Hyperkeratosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Short stature", "Blackout", "Hot flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Knee pain", "Tunnel vision", "Kussmaul's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Crepitus", "Cotton wool spots", "Internal bleeding", "Ventricular tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Hematospermia", "Clouding of consciousness", "Bronchiectasis", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Erectile dysfunction", "Xeroderma", "Shivering", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Cullen's sign", "Indigestion", "Nocturnal Cough", "Orofacial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Nipple discharge", "Joint pain", "Formication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Pain", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Hyperesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Xeroderma", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Ecchymosis", "Facial nerve paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Vaginal odor", "Sleep apnea", "Hegar's sign", "Fourth heart sound"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Nodule", "Sore throat", "Hypoesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Pursed lip breathing", "Cachexia", "Hemiplegia", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Vasoconstriction", "Breast lump", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Edema", "Excessive Crying", "Vomiting", "Primarily Obsessional OCD"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Globus pharyngis", "Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Tachycardia", "Proctitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Nosebleed", "Hypokinesia", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Hemoperitoneum", "Hypersexuality", "Pseudologia fantastica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Disinhibition", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Skin ulcer", "Syncope"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Genital wart", "Hyperphosphatemia", "Thought disorder", "Levine's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Hiccup", "Rhonchi", "Bradycardia", "Vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Sexual dysfunction", "Microalbuminuria", "Hypercholesterolemia", "Lightheadedness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Myocardial infarction?", "answers": ["Feeling of impending doom", "Labored breathing", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Blepharospasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Splenomegaly", "Optic neuritis", "Paresthesia", "Monomelic amyotrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Bleeding", "Lumbago", "Hyperhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Scaly skin", "Pelvic pain", "Agitation", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Brittle nails", "Balance disorder", "Lethargy", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Cardiac asthma", "Mastodynia", "Costovertebral angle tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Osler's sign", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Water retention", "Uveitis", "Tumor", "Suicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Pain behind the eyes", "Glossodynia", "Vaginal tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Pursed lip breathing", "Dandruff", "Flaccid paralysis", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Tonsillitis", "Hyperglycemia", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Pretibial myxedema", "Fibrosis", "Rectal prolapse", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Spasmodic dysphonia", "Bouchard's nodes", "Hyperventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Headache", "Tumor", "Stuttering", "Loss of smell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anxiety disorder?", "answers": ["Urinary Frequency", "Wheeze", "Abdominal pain", "Anhedonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Agitation", "Amenorrhoea", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Microalbuminuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Watery eyes", "Labored breathing", "Numbness of the face or tongue", "Erythema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Syncope", "Neck pain", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Tinnitus", "Neck pain", "Aggression", "Maculopapular rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Pus", "Dysmenorrhea", "Bigger mole diameter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Internal bleeding", "Major depression", "Fever", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Compulsive hoarding", "Cough", "Esophageal varices", "Major depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Shock", "Runny nose", "Dementia", "Ileus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Cold sensitivity", "Thought insertion", "Fatigue", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Tophus", "Vomiting", "Conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Measles?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Pain", "Delayed puberty", "Acute bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Hyperglycemia", "Stomatitis", "Syncope"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Bleeding diathesis", "Sexual obsessions", "Enthesitis", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Echolalia", "Hyperkeratosis", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Phonological deficit", "Levine's sign", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Constipation", "Ecchymosis", "Thyroid nodule", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Flatulence", "Burning Chest Pain", "Vision disorder", "Night Sweats"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Frequent urination", "Angina Pectoris", "Anasarca", "Pathological laughing and crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Middle back pain", "Chancre", "Seborrheic dermatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Polyphagia", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Swelling", "Pus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Hypoglycemia", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Somnolence", "Crepitus", "Swollen legs", "Stereotypy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Intellectual disability", "Gingival recession", "Poor wound healing", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Bronchiectasis", "Emaciation", "Cramp", "Speech disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Opisthotonus", "Disinhibition", "Acne", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Blurred vision", "Wheals"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Polydipsia", "Bacterial vaginosis", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Raynaud's phenomenon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Anhidrosis", "Gingival enlargement", "Xerostomia", "Major depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Mania", "Hypervigilance", "Cyst", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Dysphoria", "Hyperacusis", "Self-harm", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Parosmia", "Immunodeficiency", "Irritability", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Glycosuria", "Hearing problem", "Swollen testicle", "Colitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Acanthosis nigricans", "Otorrhea", "Heart murmur", "Forgetfulness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Indigestion", "Meningitis", "Difficulty Focusing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Swollen feet", "Crepitus", "Hallucination", "Urinary tract infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Osler's sign", "Bruxism", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Lipodystrophy", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Dacryoadenitis", "Radiculopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Formication", "Quadriplegia", "Pleuritic chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Azotemia", "Hematoma", "Optic neuritis", "Weight gain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Formication", "Hemiparesis", "Brain damage", "Laryngitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Infection", "Hegar's sign", "Tendonitis", "Wheals"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Bone fracture", "Gastric varices", "Nocturnal enuresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Paresthesia", "Delirium", "Acne", "Metrorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Diabetes mellitus?", "answers": ["Tendonitis", "Mental confusion", "Swelling", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Vascular Leak", "Shock", "Disinhibition", "Myopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Acalculia", "Cotton wool spots", "Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Impetigo", "Psychosis", "Polyphagia", "cerebella tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Myoclonus", "Sundowning", "Feeling of impending doom", "Nerve injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Asymmetry", "Hypersomnia", "Night Sweats", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Toe walking", "Nerve injury", "Anterograde amnesia", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Pale feces", "Irritability", "Audible pop at time of injury", "Rectal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Wandering", "Leukorrhea", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Meningitis", "Phlegm", "Hirano body"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Amnesia", "Bleeding diathesis", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Neck pain", "Dandruff", "Emaciation", "Retrograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Apathy", "Golden S sign", "Disregard for right and wrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Paraphasia", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Dizziness", "Proctitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Fasciculation", "Delayed onset muscle soreness", "Pathological laughing and crying", "Dysuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Hallucination", "Hypotension", "Chills", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Euphoria", "Nail clubbing", "Delusion", "Iron deficiency"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Inverted nipple", "Major depression", "Dehydration", "Bone fracture"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Delirium", "Feeling of impending doom", "Hyperactivity", "Apraxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Hypercapnia", "Aphasia", "Opisthotonus", "Tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Pursed lip breathing", "Agnosia", "Painful ejaculation", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Extreme Weight Loss", "Urinary incontinence", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Rebound tenderness", "Agitation", "Brittle nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Hepatosplenomegaly", "Numbness of face", "Nosebleed", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Pulmonary edema", "Aggression", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Myelopathy", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alzheimer's disease?", "answers": ["Loss of smell", "Gingivitis", "Difficulty Focusing", "Necrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Myocardial infarction", "Immunodeficiency", "Optic neuritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Boredom", "Malaise", "Change in sexual interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Hemolytic anemia", "Poor wound healing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Nasal polyp", "Tachylalia", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Fever", "Runny nose", "Hydrocele", "Pericarditis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Fatigue", "Acute bronchitis", "Phonological deficit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Cerebral hemorrhage", "Hyperlipidemia", "Wheeze", "Optic neuritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic bronchitis?", "answers": ["Bigger mole diameter", "Genital ulcer", "Thrombosis", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Suicidal ideation", "Polydipsia", "Anorexia", "Angina Pectoris"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Dizziness", "Chemosis", "Vision disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Nephrotic syndrome", "Self-harm", "Vaginitis", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Depression", "Glycosuria", "Lack of Concentration", "Markle sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Cirrhosis", "Delusion", "Snoring", "Narcissism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Erythema nodosum", "Anxiety", "Photophobia", "Cardiac asthma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Hyperactivity", "Bruise", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Dysphoria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Vaginitis", "Angina Pectoris", "Kehr's sign", "Impulsivity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Malar rash", "Oral candidiasis", "Restricted behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Microalbuminuria", "Delirium", "Fatigue", "Paranoia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Borderline personality disorder?", "answers": ["Vasoconstriction", "Risky behavior", "Weight loss", "Spider angioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Phyllodes tumor", "Pelvic pain", "Dysphagia", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Skin Discoloration", "Vaginal bleeding", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Pyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Osteophyte", "Weight loss", "Impulsivity", "Swollen feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Nipple discharge", "Anorexia", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Tetany", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Rectal bleeding", "Post-nasal drip"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cervical cancer?", "answers": ["Avolition", "Cervical cancer", "Pus", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Hypoxia", "Lack of empathy", "Myerson's sign", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Wart", "Myerson's sign", "Bradypnea", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Parosmia", "Dysphonia", "Depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Floater", "Fever", "Markle sign", "Verbosity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Stupor", "Weight loss", "Tophus", "Inferiority complex"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Gingivitis", "Lhermitte's sign", "Hydrocele"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Coprolalia", "Coprolalia", "Pharyngitis", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Panic attack", "Menorrhagia", "Bradypnea", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Frontal release sign", "Glossitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Bleeding on probing", "Muscle pain", "Cracked Skin", "Vesical tenesmus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Nodule", "Crackles", "Melena", "Jaundice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Vision loss", "Leg pain", "Auditory hallucination", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hepatitis A?", "answers": ["Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Asymptomatic", "Myerson's sign", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Amenorrhoea", "Polyphagia", "Hypomania", "Post-void dribbling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Fetor hepaticus", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Waxy flexibility", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Hypervigilance", "Bigger mole diameter", "Sleep disturbances", "Polyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Rectal tenesmus", "Atrophy", "Facial swelling", "Ketoacidosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Bounding pulse", "Shock", "Cramp", "Peripheral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Glossodynia", "Hyperglycemia", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Vascular Leak"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Hot flash", "Chemosis", "Weight loss", "Abdominal obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Pressure of speech", "Tic", "Fatigue", "Agitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Polydipsia", "Hepatosplenomegaly", "Shock", "Catatonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Type 1 diabetes?", "answers": ["Nerve injury", "Stroke", "Glycosuria", "Decreased level of consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Crepitus", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Rhonchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Markle sign", "Body ache", "Sore throat", "Hyperkeratosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Collapse", "Myocardial infarction", "Apraxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Hepatosplenomegaly", "Heart murmur", "Hiccup", "Fox's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Social isolation", "Hematemesis", "Rhinitis", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Speech delay", "Chest pain", "Frequent urination", "Amenorrhoea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Esophageal cancer?", "answers": ["Pectus carinatum", "Risky behavior", "Breast lump", "Dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Flashback", "Melena", "Balance disorder", "Myoclonus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Photosensitivity", "Syncope", "Spinal tumor", "Hormonal disorders"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Fecal incontinence", "Hematemesis", "Verbosity", "Anterograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Anemia", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Anorexia", "Goitre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Psychomotor retardation", "Indigestion", "Esophageal varices", "Tonsillitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Heartburn", "Steatorrhea", "Intellectual disability", "Obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Thyroid nodule", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Erythema nodosum", "Impetigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Nuchal Rigidity", "Dizziness", "Melancholia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Eczema", "Crepitus", "Blood in stool", "Erythema nodosum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Abdominal mass", "Vomiting", "Mental illness", "cerebella tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Hypertriglyceridemia", "Night terror", "Delayed onset muscle soreness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Hypocalcaemia", "Nausea", "Hypercapnia", "Gynecologic hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Swollen lymph nodes", "Short stature", "Splenomegaly", "Pallor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Rumination", "/m/0lxt", "Sensorineural hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Groin Lump", "Hiccup", "Hyperkalemia", "Glossitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peptic ulcer?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Tic", "Hirano body", "Personality or behavior changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Anasarca", "Night Sweats", "Cerebral hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Stuttering", "Biliary colic", "Pica", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Post-nasal drip", "Scaly skin", "Lightheadedness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Dark urine", "Vaginal discharge", "Middle back pain", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Malocclusion", "Delirium"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Skin rash", "Renal failure", "Post-nasal drip"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Inverted nipple", "Nerve injury", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Hyperglycemia", "Weight gain", "Weight loss", "Catatonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Atrophy", "Hyperkeratosis", "Stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["Hunger", "Vaginal bleeding", "Nikolsky's sign", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Arthritis?", "answers": ["/m/0lxt", "Vaginitis", "Dyspnea", "Dermatosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Agnosia", "Paresthesia", "Fibrosis", "Periorbital puffiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Ataxia", "Collapse", "Snoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Purpura", "Clouding of consciousness", "Weight loss", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Sensorineural hearing loss", "Enthesitis", "Erythema nodosum", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Delayed reading ability", "Otalgia", "Pain", "Toe walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Hemoptysis", "Koilonychia", "Anal swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Swelling", "Erectile dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Hypertriglyceridemia", "Seizure", "Hemiplegia", "Choreoathetosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Fibromyalgia", "Thrombocytopenia", "Mental illness", "Lethargy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Anal discharge", "Restricted behavior", "Mouth ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Iron deficiency", "Hypogonadism", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Pulsus paradoxus", "Odynophagia", "Major depressive episode", "Numbness of face"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Coprolalia", "Clonus", "Hirano body", "Chills"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Depression", "Menorrhagia", "Hyperkeratosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Oligomenorrhea", "Enophthalmia", "Dysesthesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Gingival recession", "Hyperreflexia", "Wheals", "Blank Stare"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Dry cough", "Polyneuropathy", "Vesicle", "Blurred vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Dry Eye", "Dysphagia", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Intestinal Obstruction", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Palilalia", "Raynaud's phenomenon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Clouding of consciousness", "Breast lump", "Periorbital puffiness", "Vision loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Chorioretinitis", "Nuchal Rigidity", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Social isolation", "Myocardial infarction", "Sexual dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Frontal release sign", "Paraphasia", "Menorrhagia", "Paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Neck pain", "Stiffness", "Swollen legs", "Pallor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Rectal pain", "Scotoma", "Avoidant personality disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Lumbago", "Urinary retention", "Urinary Frequency"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Hives", "Halos around lights", "Muscle Spasms", "Laryngitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Dandruff", "Kussmaul's sign", "Hypertonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Coma", "Fatigue", "Xerophthalmia", "Morphea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Pruritus", "Lethargy", "Vital Exhaustion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Uveitis", "Blumberg sign", "Hypercapnia", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Melena", "Paraphasia", "Bruise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Shivering", "Compulsive hoarding", "Inverted nipple", "Delirium"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Optic neuritis", "Azotemia", "Cotton wool spots", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Schizophasia", "Convulsion", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Compulsive hoarding", "Vertigo", "Hematemesis", "Dysentery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Balance disorder", "Rumination", "Enophthalmia", "Froment's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Thought disorder", "Cold sensitivity", "Phlegm", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Gingivitis", "Enophthalmia", "Abdominal mass", "Sweating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Breast lump", "Urinary incontinence", "Blepharospasm", "Coagulopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Breakthrough bleeding", "Toe walking", "Erythema multiforme"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Brain damage", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Hepatosplenomegaly", "Pressure of speech"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Indigestion", "Lymphocytopenia", "Constipation", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Nystagmus", "Syncope", "Glycosuria", "Opisthotonus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Avolition", "Diplopia", "Akathisia", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Periorbital puffiness", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism", "Stunted growth", "Spasticity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "Hyperthermia", "Paranoia", "Rebound tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Convulsion", "Cervicitis", "Fasciculation", "Obturator sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Synovitis", "Lhermitte's sign", "Uremia", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Lactose intolerance", "Chorioretinitis", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Maculopapular rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Multiple sclerosis?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Indigestion", "Nervousness", "Myelopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Chemosis", "Skin tag", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Diarrhea", "Impetigo", "Feeling of impending doom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Dermatitis", "Stroke", "Audible pop at time of injury", "Psychosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Toothache", "Excessive Crying", "Purpura", "Chorioretinitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Constipation", "Painless testicular lump", "Hypocalcaemia", "Genital sores"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Gait abnormality", "Post-nasal drip", "Hypomania"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Dysmenorrhea", "Fatigue", "Hypoxemia", "Hypomimia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Delayed reading ability", "Optic neuritis", "Nightmare", "Hyperglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "Bell's palsy", "Rhonchi", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Boredom", "Cold sensitivity", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Pancreatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Obturator sign", "Dupuytren's contracture", "Difficulty Focusing", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrhythmia", "Enanthem", "Hormonal disorders", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Rectal bleeding", "Cachexia", "Hormonal disorders", "Avoidant personality disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Coagulopathy", "Palmar erythema", "Pain behind the eyes", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Polyuria", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Insomnia", "Hemoperitoneum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Bleeding gums", "Suicidal ideation", "Stereotypy", "Substance-related disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Night terror", "Glycosuria", "Sadness", "Frontal release sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Chorioretinitis", "Pelvic pain", "Bruxism", "Angina Pectoris"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Narrow stools", "Panic attack", "Purpura"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Vision loss", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Snoring", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Abscess", "Self-harm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Leukocytosis", "Inferiority complex", "Myelopathy", "Social isolation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Astasia-abasia", "Anxiety", "Pectus carinatum", "Pulsus paradoxus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Peripheral neuropathy", "Renal colic", "Anger", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Psychomotor retardation", "Cramp", "Chemosis", "Opisthotonus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Dysphoria", "Asthma", "Irregular menstruation", "Shallow breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Pharyngitis", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Fox's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Agitation", "Ritualistic behavior", "Eosinophilia", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Facial pain", "Foul smelling urine", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Sleep disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Echolalia", "Dermatosis", "Guilt", "Rhonchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Bone fracture", "Hypokinesia", "Wart", "Mood swing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Melancholia", "Snoring", "Malar rash", "Dacryoadenitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Polyneuropathy", "Sexual dysfunction", "Vesical tenesmus", "Left ventricular hypertrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Chronic pain", "Lack of Remorse", "Kehr's sign", "Infertility"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Rovsing's sign", "Phonological deficit", "Back pain", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Sexual obsessions", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Urinary urgency"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Hallucination", "Renal colic", "Agnosia", "Cotton wool spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Nystagmus", "Balance disorder", "Eye pain", "Intrusive thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Bone fracture", "Rumination", "Hypercapnia", "Chorea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Urinary tract infection", "Diplopia", "Internal bleeding", "Depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Deafness", "Dizziness", "Swollen testicle", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Purpura", "Eye pain", "Chest pain", "Delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Cloudy urine", "Hyperlipidemia", "Substance abuse", "Malnutrition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Anhedonia", "Genital ulcer", "Malar rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Scaly skin", "Hunger", "Delirium", "Myocardial infarction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Major depression?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Hyperesthesia", "Irritability", "Difficulty walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Parkinsonism", "Hematuria", "Hormonal disorders", "Postural instability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Spasticity", "Pneumonia", "Swelling", "Peripheral neuropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Agnosia", "Stiffness", "Parkinsonism", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anterior cruciate ligament injury?", "answers": ["Dieting", "Testicle pain", "Urinary tract infection", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Bigger mole diameter", "Disinhibition", "Pallor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Hematospermia", "Fasciculation", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Nocturia", "Loss of smell", "Vision disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Joint pain", "Facial pain", "Psoas sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Proctitis", "Albuminuria", "Malar rash", "Arthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Anal discharge", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Groin Lump", "Abdominal distension", "Pus", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Diarrhea", "Chest pain", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Scotoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Abdominal pain", "Bronchiectasis", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Rectal pain", "Nodule", "Myxedema", "/m/0lxt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Mouth breathing", "Lumbago", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Syncope"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Penile discharge", "Markle sign", "Boredom"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Pain", "Palpitation", "Oral candidiasis", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Sinusitis", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Chest Tightness", "Breakthrough bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Hunger", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Dysuria", "Stereotypy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Middle back pain", "Dysphonia", "Sweating", "Abnormal vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Pelvic pain", "Ageusia", "Flushing", "Xerostomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Flu-like syndrome", "Post-nasal drip", "Hematoma", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Restless legs syndrome", "Asterixis", "Nausea", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Stiff neck", "Hyperventilation", "Pyuria", "Hyperreflexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Hematuria", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Self-harm", "Vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Night Sweats", "Leukorrhea", "Dupuytren's contracture", "Telangiectasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Phyllodes tumor", "Testicle pain", "Vasculitis", "Hypoglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Menorrhagia", "Neuralgia", "Pain behind the eyes", "Red eye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Hydrocele", "Dyspareunia", "Goitre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chlamydia infection?", "answers": ["Nodule", "Vaginal bleeding", "Agitation", "Hegar's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Neonatal jaundice?", "answers": ["Candidiasis", "Swollen feet", "Dysphagia", "Nephritic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Neonatal jaundice?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Tenderness", "Gingival enlargement", "Snoring"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Neonatal jaundice?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Groin Lump", "Cough", "Malar rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Postpartum depression?", "answers": ["Nipple tenderness", "Hyperventilation", "Insomnia", "Pulmonary consolidation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Tinnitus", "Morphea", "Stupor", "Sensorineural hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Dehydration", "Astasia-abasia", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Syncope", "Eosinophilia", "Akathisia", "Foul smelling urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Sleep apnea", "Arthropathy", "Apnea", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Golden S sign", "Hearing problem", "Muscle atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Biliary colic", "Photophobia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Proctitis", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Glossitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Alopecia", "Mental confusion", "Trismus", "Pathological laughing and crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Nasal polyp", "Pica", "Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Coagulopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Koilonychia", "Heart murmur", "Chorioretinitis", "Short stature"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Hypoxia", "Clouding of consciousness", "Amnesia", "Urinary incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Gingival enlargement", "Myerson's sign", "Fatigue", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Angular cheilitis", "Sweating", "Short stature", "Ptosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Pale feces", "Menorrhagia", "Hypoesthesia", "Intrusive thoughts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Pallor", "Bleeding gums", "Proctitis", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Dry Eye", "Coprolalia", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Purpura", "Hyperhidrosis", "Erectile dysfunction", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Dehydration", "Dyspnea", "Tetany", "Ageusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Eructation", "Somnolence", "Loss of smell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Fasciculation", "Obturator sign", "Hallucination", "Cervical cancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Depression", "Radiculopathy", "Border irregularity", "Sputum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Nasal polyp", "Rectal tenesmus", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Restless legs syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Stomatitis", "Rose spots", "Malaise", "Dermatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Iron deficiency anemia?", "answers": ["Irritability", "Narcissism", "Pruritus ani", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Steatorrhea", "Coma", "Pulmonary hypertension", "Urge incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Stiffness", "Bruise", "Aphasia", "Hyperhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Silhouette sign", "Rheumatoid nodule", "Hyperreflexia", "Hyperpigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Emaciation", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Retching"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Gait abnormality", "Skin ulcer", "Diplopia", "Abscess"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Dysmenorrhea", "Tinnitus", "Hyperhidrosis", "Ataxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Headache", "Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Blister", "Osteoporosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Balance disorder", "Erectile dysfunction", "Bubo", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Dactylitis", "Nipple discharge", "Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Enophthalmia", "Nystagmus", "Facial pain", "Cerebellar ataxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Nightmare", "Chronic cough", "Quadriplegia", "Delayed onset muscle soreness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Fecal incontinence", "Meningitis", "Red eye", "Spasticity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Flaccid paralysis", "Chronic cough", "Microalbuminuria", "Silhouette sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Bleeding diathesis", "Hyperacusis", "Facial Paresis", "Arthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Stuttering", "Muscle Spasms", "Cerebral hemorrhage", "Albuminuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Self-destructive behaviour", "Hematospermia", "Hydrocele", "Dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Lack of empathy", "Vision loss", "Dieting", "Delayed puberty"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Hemiplegia", "Bounding pulse", "Urethritis", "Hyperlipidemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Stridor", "Pancolitis", "Floater", "Difficulty walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Bacterial vaginosis", "Hyperesthesia", "Globus pharyngis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Cardiac arrest", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Thought disorder", "Numbness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Rectal bleeding", "Urethritis", "Vision disorder", "Hyperglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Change in sexual interest", "Apraxia", "Speech delay", "Coagulopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Delirium", "Cirrhosis", "Dystonia", "Vertigo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stroke?", "answers": ["Dyschezia", "Mental confusion", "Keratitis", "Inverted nipple"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Anhidrosis", "Vaginitis", "Erythema chronicum migrans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Polyuria", "Watery diarrhea", "Xeroderma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Flatulence", "Chest Tightness", "Facial nerve paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Vaginal discharge", "Impetigo", "Blank Stare", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Acne", "Glossodynia", "Mood swing", "Swollen feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Chorea", "Morphea", "Orthopnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Leukorrhea", "Heartburn", "Ileus", "Heart murmur"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Spinal tumor", "Dry cough", "Fatty liver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Xerophthalmia", "Stiffness", "Body ache"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Stiff neck", "Dysesthesia", "Pruritus ani", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Impetigo", "Clouding of consciousness", "Schizophasia", "Blank Stare"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Hemiplegia", "Meningism", "Air crescent sign", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Cloudy urine", "Hyperhidrosis", "Pallor", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Palpitation", "Narrow stools", "Hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Tendonitis", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Fibromyalgia", "Mastodynia", "Itchy eyes", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Anhidrosis", "Vaginal tenderness", "Lack of Remorse", "Forgetfulness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Dandruff", "Obturator sign", "Anxiety", "Cloudy urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Delayed reading ability", "Substance abuse", "Silhouette sign", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Pain", "Telangiectasia", "Osler's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Peripheral neuropathy", "Stereotypy", "Erythema", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Polyneuropathy", "Myerson's sign", "Orthostatic hypotension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Retrograde amnesia", "Purpura", "Skin tag", "Skin rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Intertrigo", "Necrosis", "Pharyngitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Candidiasis?", "answers": ["Rectal prolapse", "Spasticity", "Forgetfulness", "Blister"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Myoclonus", "Astasia-abasia", "Stiffness", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Steatorrhea", "Dermatosis", "Irritability", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Myopathy", "Verbosity", "Rheumatoid nodule", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Carelessness", "Meningism", "Clonus", "Erectile dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Pain behind the eyes", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Epilepsy?", "answers": ["Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Blank Stare", "Delayed milestone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sciatica?", "answers": ["Golden S sign", "Bone tumor", "Knee pain", "Water retention"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Sciatica?", "answers": ["Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Bradycardia", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Fever", "Infertility", "Wandering"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Dyspnea", "Urge incontinence", "Tendonitis", "Painful ejaculation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Bleeding gums", "Facial nerve paralysis", "Sadness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Nosebleed", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Acalculia", "Lack of empathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Levine's sign", "Dermatitis", "Hypomania", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Anorexia", "Erythema multiforme", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Floater", "Runny nose", "Vesicle", "Infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Emotional insecurity", "Bouchard's nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "answers": ["Glossitis", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Retching", "Dysosmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Peripheral neuropathy?", "answers": ["Hypogonadism", "Dehydration", "Fox's sign", "Muscle weakness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Cerebellar ataxia", "Dyspnea", "Orthopnea", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Ecchymosis", "Chest pain", "Tachycardia", "Xerostomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Upper respiratory tract infection", "Anhidrosis", "Mole color changes", "Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Formication", "Stridor", "Bouchard's nodes", "Arthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Neuralgia", "Glabellar reflex", "Wart", "Air crescent sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Vasculitis", "Dysphonia", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Wheeze", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Tunnel vision", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Hypomimia", "Quadriplegia", "Golden S sign", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Toe walking", "Flaccid paralysis", "Dysmenorrhea", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Hypersalivation", "Hypertension", "Dysphagia", "Frontal release sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Compulsive hoarding", "Hemoperitoneum", "Pain", "Spinal tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Restless legs syndrome", "Leukoplakia", "Nail clubbing", "Leukoplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Pulmonary consolidation", "Hematochezia", "Conjunctivitis", "Cervicitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Xerostomia", "Menorrhagia", "Fatigue", "Chronic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Gingival enlargement", "Personality or behavior changes", "Skin lesion", "Sputum"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Impulsivity", "Infection", "Compulsive behavior", "Acne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Hot flash", "Gingival enlargement", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Desquamation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Blank Stare", "Arthropathy", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Cerebellar ataxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Amenorrhoea", "Tremor", "Horner's syndrome", "Skin tag"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Melancholia", "Hypoxemia", "Hirano body", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Eye discharge", "Palmar erythema", "Bone pain", "Nuchal Rigidity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Osler's sign", "Hemoptysis", "Neuralgia", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Cachexia", "Runny nose", "Hirano body", "Hyperlipidemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lung cancer?", "answers": ["Cough", "Anasarca", "Urinary tract infection", "Tonsillitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Acute liver failure?", "answers": ["Nystagmus", "Hypomania", "Asterixis", "Anal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine", "Blepharospasm", "Stereotypy", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Opportunistic infection", "Angular cheilitis", "Dysphoria", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Pelvic pain", "Knee pain", "Thought disorder", "Agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Lack of Remorse", "Pain", "Suicidal ideation", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Immunodeficiency", "Bradykinesia", "Convulsion", "Grandiose delusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Self-harm", "Risus sardonicus", "Jaundice", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Pain", "Echolalia", "Ascites", "Meningitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Hepatosplenomegaly", "Intestinal Obstruction", "Social isolation", "Lower motor neuron lesion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Nuchal Rigidity", "Dyskinesia", "Vital Exhaustion", "Mouth breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Swelling", "Anger", "Clonus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Keratitis", "Thought insertion", "Cough", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Emotional insecurity", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Leg pain", "Anhedonia", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Joint effusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Hyperhidrosis", "Vasculitis", "Nephrotic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Heartburn", "Catatonia", "Scotoma", "Breast lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Breakthrough bleeding", "Dysautonomia", "Psychomotor retardation", "Caput medusae"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Floater", "Collapse", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Aggression"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Kaposi's sarcoma", "Anxiety", "Nikolsky's sign", "Pericarditis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Urinary tract infection", "Psychosis", "Hirano body"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Short stature", "Hypocalcaemia", "Narrow stools", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Mental confusion", "Vaginitis", "Leukoplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Apnea", "Inflammation", "Avolition", "Retching"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Cold sensitivity", "Bradypnea", "Hemiplegia", "Frontal release sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Homicidal ideation", "Intermittent claudication", "Facial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Auditory hallucination", "Carelessness", "Sleep disturbances", "Phlebitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Dysentery", "Bigger mole diameter", "Change in bowel habits", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Bronchophony", "Myerson's sign", "Hematospermia", "Waxy flexibility"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Phonophobia", "Phonological deficit", "Apathy", "Heart murmur"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Schizophrenia?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Splenomegaly", "Stupor", "Substance abuse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Aphasia", "Lethargy", "Anterograde amnesia", "Weight gain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Apraxia", "Dyspareunia", "Bone fracture", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Dysgeusia", "Post-void dribbling", "Abdominal mass", "Glossitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Cerebellar ataxia", "Nausea", "Muehrcke's nails", "Vaginal tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Osteophyte", "Wart", "Hirsutism", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Labored breathing", "Leukocytosis", "Cramp", "Hemiparesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Ascites", "Fatty liver", "Vision disorder", "Halitosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Albuminuria", "Oliguria", "Amenorrhoea", "Stridor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Pain", "Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Flashback", "Risky behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Trismus", "Xerophthalmia", "Osteoporosis", "Abdominal distension"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Bleeding", "Collapse", "Vesical tenesmus", "Sleep deprivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Stomatitis", "Osteophyte", "Irregular menstruation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Loss of interest", "Mastodynia", "Cyst"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Nocturnal enuresis", "Mole color changes", "Speech delay", "Intestinal Obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Dermatosis", "Persistent urge to urinate", "Dysfunctional uterine bleeding", "Pneumatosis intestinalis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Colitis", "Urge incontinence", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Stomatitis", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Anal swelling", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Swelling", "Pleuritic chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Impetigo", "Back pain", "Collapse", "Auditory hallucination"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Portal hypertension", "Dysmenorrhea", "Neck pain", "Persistent urge to urinate"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Fecal incontinence", "Trismus", "Poor wound healing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Fecal incontinence", "Vomiting", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Stereotypy", "Abdominal pain", "Spinal tumor", "Sadness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Arthropathy", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Risus sardonicus", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Ovarian cyst?", "answers": ["Hyperventilation", "Metrorrhagia", "Mania", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Blood in stool", "Mouth breathing", "Sensorineural hearing loss", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Nocturnal Cough", "Flushing", "Pursed lip breathing", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Dysuria", "Intrusive thoughts", "Vesical tenesmus", "Hyperhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Blumberg sign", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Asymptomatic", "Numbness of the face or tongue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Obesity", "Leukorrhea", "Vascular Leak", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Dupuytren's contracture", "Vaginal tenderness", "Hemiparesis", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Bone pain", "Swollen legs", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Change in sexual interest", "Ritualistic behavior", "Delayed puberty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bacterial vaginosis?", "answers": ["Enthesitis", "Agnosia", "Pruritus", "Desquamation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Constipation", "Excessive Crying", "Bruxism", "Seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Depression", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Hypoesthesia", "Thought disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Numbness of face", "Hyperthermia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Hypomania", "Compulsive behavior", "Splenomegaly", "Lethargy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Choreoathetosis", "Flatulence", "Meningitis", "Emaciation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Neuralgia", "Mental confusion", "Diarrhea", "Lymphocytosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Acute abdomen", "Rectal tenesmus", "Mole color changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Thrombosis", "Panic attack", "Wart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Irritable bowel syndrome?", "answers": ["Maculopapular rash", "Abdominal pain", "Hot flash", "Bounding pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Glossodynia", "Joint pain", "Pharyngitis", "Bone tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Dry Eye", "Leukorrhea", "Breast lump", "Terry's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Asymmetry", "Major depressive episode", "Phonological deficit", "Malar rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Renal failure", "Chest pain", "Stereotypy", "Inferiority complex"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Nerve injury", "Hypersexuality", "Compulsive hoarding", "Weight gain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Abdominal pain", "Dyspnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Nocturnal enuresis", "Mole color changes", "Water retention", "Wandering"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Pericarditis", "Muscle Spasms", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Neuralgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Joint stiffness", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Skin lesion", "Personality or behavior changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Nephrotic syndrome", "Glossodynia", "Bleeding diathesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Joint effusion", "Fatigue", "Leukopenia", "Froment's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Vital Exhaustion", "Weight loss", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Scaly skin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Nail clubbing", "Hot flash", "Depression", "Shallow breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Bruise", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Homicidal ideation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Echolalia", "Fever", "Vital Exhaustion", "Labored breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lupus erythematosus?", "answers": ["Acanthosis nigricans", "Photopsia", "Malnutrition", "Amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Hemiplegia", "Anxiety", "Collapse", "Nocturnal enuresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Lumbago", "Muscle weakness", "Red eye", "Breakthrough bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Atrophy", "Xerostomia", "Social isolation", "Hematemesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Malocclusion", "Painless testicular lump", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Malocclusion", "Ecchymosis", "Stridor", "Unintentional Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Fever", "Wheeze", "Inferiority complex"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Watery diarrhea", "Vaginal odor", "Rectal bleeding", "Bruise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Dark urine", "Nocturia", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Bronchophony", "cerebella tumor", "Malaise", "Ptosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Vascular Leak", "Muscle atrophy", "Swelling", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Petechia", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Nipple discharge", "Dysautonomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Malocclusion", "Muscle atrophy", "Pain behind the eyes", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Avolition", "Chills", "Cyanosis", "Hutchinson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Eye discharge", "High Fever", "Dystonia", "Mania"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Eczema", "Anorexia", "Fetor hepaticus", "Periorbital puffiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Pathological laughing and crying", "Pus", "Leukopenia", "Cardiac arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Bleeding on probing", "Diaphoresis", "Bone tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Inverted nipple", "Bleeding", "Dysphoria", "Pericarditis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Joint stiffness", "Dissociative disorder", "Muscle pain", "Increased vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Vasoconstriction", "Hyperkeratosis", "Hydrocele", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Leukoplakia", "Dysosmia", "Albuminuria", "Shivering"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Palpitation", "Joint pain", "Facial Paresis", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Photopsia", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Back pain", "Gynecologic hemorrhage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Maculopapular rash", "Bronchophony", "Panic attack", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Tremor", "Sensorineural hearing loss", "Panic attack", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Delayed milestone", "Vertigo", "Internal bleeding", "Flu-like syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Pericarditis", "Frequent urination", "Disinhibition", "Bleeding diathesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Hunger", "Thrombocytopenia", "Spasticity", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Flushing", "Intertrigo", "Angina Pectoris", "Necrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Delayed onset muscle soreness", "Retrograde amnesia", "Hypokinesia", "Sore throat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Dengue fever?", "answers": ["Intermittent claudication", "Vasoconstriction", "Encephalopathy", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Lower motor neuron lesion", "Xerophthalmia", "cerebella tumor", "Hematuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Lymphocytopenia", "Skin rash", "Back pain", "Sneeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Hemiparesis", "Frequent urination", "Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Golden S sign", "Bigger mole diameter", "Anorexia", "Tonic\u2013clonic seizure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Fibrosis", "Dysuria", "Vaginal discharge", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Bladder cancer?", "answers": ["Glossitis", "Rectal prolapse", "Abdominal pain", "Fatty liver"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Malaria?", "answers": ["Difficulty starting and maintaining a steady stream of urine", "Swollen feet", "Chills", "Acute bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Malaria?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Bouchard's nodes", "Sensorineural hearing loss", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Indigestion", "Nausea", "Vascular Leak", "Opisthotonus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Markle sign", "Leukoplakia", "Ptosis", "Anuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Skin Discoloration", "Polyneuropathy", "Back pain", "Rectal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Rovsing's sign", "Hydrocele", "Air crescent sign", "Post-nasal drip"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Urethritis", "Bloating", "Nosebleed", "Clouding of consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Frequent urination", "Genital sores", "Malocclusion", "Hutchinson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Rectal tenesmus", "Narrow stools", "Cervicitis", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Uremia", "Heart failure", "Fetor hepaticus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Spasmodic dysphonia", "Leukocytosis", "Psychomotor retardation", "Heart failure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Seborrheic dermatitis", "Akathisia", "Fever", "Restricted behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Asymmetry", "Blumberg sign", "Hypoxia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Pain behind the eyes", "Acute abdomen", "Encephalopathy", "Furuncle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Bell's palsy", "Desquamation", "Trousseau sign of malignancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Narcissism", "Obturator sign", "Urge incontinence", "Vaginitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Urinary Frequency", "Cyanosis", "Tenderness", "Phlebitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Akathisia", "Diarrhea", "Xerostomia", "Allergic conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Vaginitis", "Diaphoresis", "Bone tumor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Increased vaginal discharge", "Nerve injury", "Rebound tenderness", "Rectal prolapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Psoas sign", "Hyperventilation", "Medulloblastoma", "Genital ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["cerebella tumor", "Enophthalmia", "Phlebitis", "Renal colic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Abdominal distension", "Hyperesthesia", "Vascular Leak", "Candidiasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Phonological deficit", "Erythema", "Acute bronchitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Hypertriglyceridemia", "Formication", "Dizziness", "Hemoptysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Otorrhea", "Heart murmur", "Wheeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Orthostatic hypotension", "Swelling", "Bronchospasm", "Malar rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Hypercholesterolemia", "Constipation", "Phlegm", "Microalbuminuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Appendicitis?", "answers": ["Gastric varices", "Vomiting", "Urge incontinence", "Toe walking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Swine influenza?", "answers": ["Intellectual disability", "Muscle pain", "Goitre", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Catatonia", "Asterixis", "Rectal bleeding", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Nipple tenderness", "Muscle atrophy", "Cachexia", "Spider angioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Wheals", "Spider angioma", "Stiffness", "Photopsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Sweating", "Substance-related disorder", "Muscle Spasms", "Enthesitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Oligomenorrhea", "Emaciation", "Osteophyte", "Erythema nodosum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Nodule", "Rhinitis", "Dry cough", "Parkinsonism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Asterixis", "Edema", "Desquamation", "Chancre"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Pericarditis", "Phyllodes tumor", "Heart failure", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Bunion", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Bradypnea", "Retrograde amnesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "cerebella tumor", "Hypokinesia", "Vaginal discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Osteoarthritis?", "answers": ["Tachypnea", "Bouchard's nodes", "Cracked Skin", "Indigestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Otorrhea", "Collapse", "Bradykinesia", "Pulsus paradoxus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Polyphagia", "Enophthalmia", "Dyspnea", "Hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Lhermitte's sign", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Body ache", "Shock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Blood in stool", "Respiratory arrest", "Markle sign", "Pleuritic chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Slurred Speech", "Cyanosis", "Wheeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Hyperactivity", "Tachypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pulmonary embolism?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Hemoptysis", "Formication", "Pelvic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Osteoporosis", "Oligomenorrhea", "Fibromyalgia", "Hutchinson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Obesity", "Granuloma", "Xerophthalmia", "Enanthem"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Depression", "Enophthalmia", "Nipple discharge", "Loose teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Hepatic encephalopathy", "Costovertebral angle tenderness", "Alopecia", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Sinusitis", "Lymphocytosis", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Seborrheic dermatitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Hirsutism", "Cervical cancer", "Hematospermia", "Chronic cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Dysphonia", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Infertility"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Nikolsky's sign", "Compulsive hoarding", "Myxedema", "Acne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Urge incontinence", "Psychomotor retardation", "Skin tag", "Hirano body"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Dark urine", "Rovsing's sign", "Amenorrhoea", "Extreme Weight Loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Type 2 diabetes", "Intertrigo", "Vision disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Polycystic ovary syndrome?", "answers": ["Fourth heart sound", "Hemiparesis", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Sexual dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Penile discharge", "Osler's sign", "Pus", "Dyskinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Enuresis", "Pruritus", "Sadness", "Coagulopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Otorrhea", "Bunion", "Candidiasis", "Pericarditis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Anal fissure", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Floater", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Compulsive behavior", "Cervicitis", "Dermatitis", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Breakthrough bleeding", "Nausea", "Water retention", "Feeling of fullness in the ear"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Swelling", "Wart", "Abdominal obesity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis externa?", "answers": ["Balance disorder", "Fever", "Hypertension", "Hepatosplenomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Hypersalivation", "Hypoxia", "Hunger", "Anal swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Cough", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Change in sexual interest", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Myelopathy", "Wart", "Labored breathing", "Formication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Anhidrosis", "Mastodynia", "Leg pain", "Cyanosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Candidiasis", "Sundowning", "Toothache", "Chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Pus", "Paresthesia", "Wheals"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Numbness of the face or tongue", "Headache", "Seizure", "Depression"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Enthesitis", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Air crescent sign", "Shallow breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Anhedonia", "Inflammation", "Constipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Dyspnea", "Lymphocytopenia", "Nocturnal enuresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Erectile dysfunction", "Vomiting", "Dry cough", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Stridor", "Acanthosis nigricans", "Pulmonary consolidation", "Knee pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Dementia", "Tachypnea", "Hyperactivity", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Toe walking", "Hyperpigmentation", "Dry Eye", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Back pain", "Obturator sign", "Racing thoughts", "Asymmetry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Sleep disorder", "Fibrosis", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Muscle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Steatorrhea", "Agnosia", "Silhouette sign", "Poor wound healing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Hematochezia", "Lack of Remorse", "Syncope"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Convulsion", "Optic neuritis", "Odynophagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Myerson's sign", "Restricted behavior", "Crackles", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Photopsia", "Lethargy", "Jaundice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Osteophyte", "Rectal pain", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Telangiectasia", "Insomnia", "Urinary Frequency", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Frontal release sign", "Chills", "Depression", "Pyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Risky behavior", "Sneeze", "Gingivitis", "Chest Tightness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Bunion", "Hematochezia", "Rhonchi", "Hypoglycemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Change in sexual interest", "Leukocytosis", "Nosebleed", "Infertility"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Melanocytic nevus", "Shivering", "Arthropathy", "Guilt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Genital wart", "Malaise", "Pancolitis", "Acne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Hemoptysis", "Stuttering", "Pleuritic chest pain", "Intermittent claudication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Microalbuminuria", "Cervical cancer", "Acute abdomen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Abscess", "Mental illness", "Hypoxemia", "Postural instability"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Wheeze", "Rumination", "Hegar's sign", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Cervicitis", "Bronchophony", "Fox's sign", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Pneumonia?", "answers": ["Clonus", "Formication", "Anorexia", "Hyperaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Grey Turner's sign", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Vomiting", "Glabellar reflex"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Ptosis", "Sleep disturbances", "Headache", "Vaginal odor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Eye discharge", "Fever", "Short stature", "Pallor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Hydrocele", "Hepatic encephalopathy", "Impetigo", "Vasculitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Metabolic acidosis", "Anorexia", "Inflammation", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Erythema chronicum migrans", "Otalgia", "Type 2 diabetes", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Painless testicular lump", "Anasarca", "Malaise", "Tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Sinusitis", "Diabetes mellitus", "Flushing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Dactylitis", "Photophobia", "Cervical lymphadenopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Hyperactivity", "Malnutrition", "Anemia", "Dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Hyperpigmentation", "Dacryoadenitis", "Tonsillitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Hives", "Apathy", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Hyperhidrosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Urinary incontinence", "Polyphagia", "Echolalia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Ascites", "Malar rash", "Halitosis", "Barrel chest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Muscle weakness", "Amnesia", "Skin rash", "Hyperaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Hypertension", "Chills", "Primarily Obsessional OCD"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Water retention", "Mental illness", "Paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Streptococcal pharyngitis?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Erythroleukoplakia", "Vaginitis", "Collapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Fungal meningitis?", "answers": ["Tendonitis", "Increased vaginal discharge", "Fever", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Fungal meningitis?", "answers": ["Asymptomatic", "Meningitis", "Pain", "Polyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Fungal meningitis?", "answers": ["Vascular Leak", "Insomnia", "Meningism", "Cracked Skin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Fungal meningitis?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Labored breathing", "Photophobia", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Fungal meningitis?", "answers": ["cerebella tumor", "Cough", "Headache", "Leukoplakia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Headache", "/m/0lxt", "Dyspnea", "Middle back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Hematoma", "Restricted behavior", "Chills", "Radiculopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Nosebleed", "Pharyngitis", "Dyskinesia", "Aphasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Swollen lymph nodes", "Anal discharge", "Skin lesion", "Deformity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Impetigo", "Bone fracture", "Cough", "Testicle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Painful ejaculation", "Dysphagia", "Psychomotor retardation", "Malar rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Granuloma", "Fever", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Verbosity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Tonsillitis?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Tonsillitis", "Astasia-abasia", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Bleeding on probing", "Somnolence", "Stridor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Hunger", "Osteophyte", "Forgetfulness", "Heartburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Dry cough", "Chemosis", "Koilonychia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Burning Chest Pain", "Intellectual disability", "Hypoxia", "Urinary tract infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Bruise", "Dysphonia", "Bruxism"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Gastroesophageal reflux disease?", "answers": ["Abnormal vaginal discharge", "Coma", "Sore throat", "Enthesitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Blister", "Hot flash", "Speech delay", "Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Loss of smell", "Hyperhidrosis", "Toothache", "Eye discharge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Nocturia", "Lack of empathy", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Dysosmia", "Wart", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Oral bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Bell's palsy", "Nikolsky's sign", "Optic neuritis", "Micrographia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Hiccup", "Paresthesia", "Vesicle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Dystonia", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Opportunistic infection", "Trousseau sign of malignancy", "Bone Loss", "Drooling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Leukorrhea", "Erythema multiforme", "Acute bronchitis", "Spasmodic dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Pyuria", "Xerophthalmia", "Somnolence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Dysentery", "Loose teeth", "Bradykinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Chills", "Hyperreflexia", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Balance disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Pruritus", "Fatigue", "Vaginal discharge", "Stroke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Hypomimia", "Genital sores", "Uremia", "Indigestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Pursed lip breathing", "Metrorrhagia", "Hallucination"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Torticollis", "Levine's sign", "Gingival recession", "Dysautonomia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Apraxia", "Internuclear ophthalmoplegia", "Meningitis", "Dysmenorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Apathy", "Oliguria", "Risus sardonicus", "Euphoria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Vascular Leak", "Xerophthalmia", "Urinary incontinence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Hyperphosphatemia", "Pneumonia", "Frequent urination", "Psychosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Melena", "Nervousness", "Seborrheic dermatitis", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Diaphoresis", "Anxiety", "Heartburn", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Gingival enlargement", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Tenderness", "Akathisia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Primarily Obsessional OCD", "Melanocytic nevus", "Labored breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Froment's sign", "Acute abdomen", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Hypotension", "Shivering", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Globus pharyngis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Gait abnormality", "Bruise", "Hunger", "Nephritic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Sleep disorder", "Meningitis", "Change in bowel habits", "Swollen feet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Bacterial vaginosis", "Bronchiectasis", "Heberden's node", "Tremor"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Photosensitivity", "Dysarthria", "Hypoxemia", "Type 2 diabetes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Border irregularity", "Constipation", "Hepatorenal syndrome", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Hyperacusis", "Gynecologic hemorrhage", "Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Wart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Blister", "Orthopnea", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Central facial palsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Night terror", "Delayed milestone", "Parosmia", "Lumbago"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Hearing problem", "Deafness", "Dementia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Chemosis", "Angina Pectoris", "Nausea", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Mouth breathing", "Red eye", "Palilalia", "Back pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Ataxia", "Genital sores", "Flu-like syndrome", "Pseudologia fantastica"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Pleuritic chest pain", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Breakthrough bleeding", "Parkinsonism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Glabellar reflex", "Intestinal varices", "Bleeding", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Numbness", "Stereotypy", "Impetigo", "Myerson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Choreoathetosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Pus", "Orthostatic hypotension", "Hot flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Postural instability", "Xerophthalmia", "Leukopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Malar rash", "Dandruff", "Amnesia", "Wheeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Cotton wool spots", "Lactose intolerance", "Acute abdomen", "Hypokinesia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Guilt", "Dysphagia", "Diplopia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Tachylalia", "Acute abdomen", "High Fever", "Myopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Hypersalivation", "Candidiasis", "Hyperreflexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Photosensitivity", "Rectal tenesmus", "Primarily Obsessional OCD"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Parkinson's disease?", "answers": ["Red eye", "Dizziness", "Blepharospasm", "Testicle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Vitamin B12 deficiency?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Swollen tonsils", "Alopecia", "Flaccid paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Carelessness", "Anal fissure", "Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Dark urine", "Pica", "Vomiting", "Bounding pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Compulsive behavior", "Splenomegaly", "Tachycardia", "Asymmetry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Shock", "Respiratory arrest", "Back pain", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Blumberg sign", "Anxiety", "Psychomotor retardation", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Abdominal pain", "Meningism", "Feeling of fullness in the ear"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Aortic aneurysm?", "answers": ["Dysphonia", "Gingival recession", "Infection", "Hyperaemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Fibrosis", "Stereotypy", "Nausea", "Mastodynia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Halos around lights", "Flushing", "Vaginal bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Collapse", "Halitosis", "Maculopapular rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Hypogonadism", "Dyspnea", "Amenorrhoea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Halos around lights", "Xeroderma", "Change in sexual interest", "Swollen legs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Dysautonomia", "Acne", "Scaly skin", "Floater"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Urinary retention", "Central facial palsy", "Headache", "Hypersalivation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Myelopathy", "Lack of Concentration", "Hypercholesterolemia", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Pelvic pain", "Medulloblastoma", "Irritability", "Gingival enlargement"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Mood swing", "Deformity", "Difficulty Focusing", "Bouchard's nodes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Premenstrual syndrome?", "answers": ["Anxiety", "Hutchinson's sign", "Rhonchi", "Somnolence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Blackout", "Sister Mary Joseph nodule", "Stuttering", "Joint stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Respiratory arrest", "Keratitis", "Hypogonadism", "Eosinophilia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Pain behind the eyes", "Hyperacusis", "Anemia", "Paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Bubo", "Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Rhonchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Wandering", "Tachypnea", "Synovitis", "Phonophobia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Bubo", "Dyspnea", "Delayed puberty", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Monomelic amyotrophy", "Chest pain", "Meningism", "Nuchal Rigidity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Tertiary hyperparathyroidism", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca", "Gynecomastia", "Bradycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Atrophy", "Bubo", "Polyphagia", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Risky behavior", "Difficulty Focusing", "Apraxia", "Rheumatoid nodule"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Ritualistic behavior", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Deformity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Phlebitis", "Back pain", "Agnosia", "Rhonchi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Sundowning", "Swelling", "Koilonychia", "Schizophasia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Muscle pain", "Restless legs syndrome", "Wandering", "Pharyngitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Hutchinson's sign", "Tetany", "Low-grade fever", "Sadness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Steatorrhea", "Nausea", "Lymphocytosis", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Dysesthesia", "Stridor", "Chest Tightness", "Vasculitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Dissociative disorder", "Cough", "Odynophagia", "Enophthalmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Laryngitis", "Tumor", "Iritis", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Inflammation", "Amenorrhoea", "Nikolsky's sign", "Slight redness of skin in ear canal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Acanthosis nigricans", "Delusion", "Amnesia", "Stiffness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Schizophasia", "Eye pain", "Joint effusion", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Nocturnal Cough", "Thyrotoxicosis", "Polyneuropathy", "Heberden's node"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Nocturnal enuresis", "Skin Discoloration", "Anorexia", "Periorbital puffiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Neck pain", "Gastric varices", "Weight loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rheumatoid arthritis?", "answers": ["Auditory hallucination", "Joint pain", "Feeling of fullness in the ear", "Pseudologia fantastica"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Lead poisoning?", "answers": ["Pulmonary consolidation", "Abdominal pain", "Anhidrosis", "/m/0lxt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis media?", "answers": ["Gastric varices", "Thought disorder", "Goitre", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis media?", "answers": ["Hearing problem", "Nerve injury", "Ptosis", "Facial pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis media?", "answers": ["Vision disorder", "Agnosia", "Otalgia", "Hives"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis media?", "answers": ["Hyperpigmentation", "Infertility", "Otorrhea", "Coprolalia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis media?", "answers": ["Splenomegaly", "Phonological deficit", "Dizziness", "Esophageal varices"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Otitis media?", "answers": ["Arthritis", "Leser\u2013Tr\u00e9lat sign", "Chancre", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Sore throat", "Pale feces", "Lack of Remorse", "Rectal prolapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Middle back pain", "Diaphoresis", "Kussmaul's sign", "Sneeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Erythema", "Tetany", "Watery eyes", "Eye pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Monomelic amyotrophy", "Fatigue", "Social isolation", "Dry cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Phlegm", "Kaposi's sarcoma", "Pharyngitis", "Hyperphosphatemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Post-nasal drip", "Sleep deprivation", "Intellectual disability", "Paralysis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Seborrheic dermatitis", "Itchy eyes", "Anhedonia", "Scotoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Joint stiffness", "Rectal tenesmus", "Insomnia", "Cotton wool spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Tachylalia", "Leukopenia", "Vaginitis", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Radiculopathy", "Lightheadedness", "Heart failure", "Loss of smell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Desquamation", "Homicidal ideation", "Hives", "Spasmodic dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Osler's sign", "Vision disorder", "Nasal congestion", "Thyrotoxicosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Disregard for right and wrong", "Runny nose", "Blister", "Shallow breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Rhinitis?", "answers": ["Nail clubbing", "Cough", "Guilt", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Hyperacusis", "Pseudologia fantastica", "Disinhibition", "Nasal congestion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Skin rash", "Toe walking", "Burning Chest Pain", "Nasal polyp"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Echolalia", "Hyperaemia", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Impulsivity", "Ketoacidosis", "Coagulopathy", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Fatty liver", "Pelvic pain", "Verbosity", "Loss of interest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Red eye", "Blurred vision", "Depression", "Scleritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Nightmare", "Major depression", "High Fever", "Tetany"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Metabolic acidosis", "Self-harm", "Hemoptysis", "Stridor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Compulsive hoarding", "Neuralgia", "Post-void dribbling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Sleep disorder", "Hepatosplenomegaly", "Tunnel vision", "Chemosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Skin tag", "Toothache", "Social isolation", "Excessive Crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Dysesthesia", "Lhermitte's sign", "Fever", "Speech delay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Guilt", "Aggression", "Sexual dysfunction", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Rose spots", "Hypocalcaemia", "Urinary retention", "Anxiety"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Sputum", "Mouth ulcer", "Stereotypy", "Hypervigilance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Air crescent sign", "Nuchal Rigidity", "Chancre", "Compulsive behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Watery eyes", "Tetany", "Apraxia", "Night Sweats"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asperger syndrome?", "answers": ["Water-electrolyte imbalance", "Stiffness", "Anger", "Dry cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Deafness", "Diarrhea", "Conductive hearing loss", "Crackles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Mental confusion", "Paralysis", "Photopsia", "Halos around lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Inferiority complex", "Facial Paresis", "Photophobia", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Pharyngitis", "Pressure of speech", "Xeroderma", "Anorexia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Hepatic encephalopathy", "Erectile dysfunction", "Markle sign", "Granuloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Pruritus ani", "Bleeding diathesis", "Microalbuminuria", "Tachypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Mental illness", "Somnolence", "Acne", "Visual verbal agnosia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Muscle Spasms", "Pancolitis", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Speech disorder", "Ascites", "Knee pain", "Testicle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Dysautonomia", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Coma", "Enanthem"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Liver failure?", "answers": ["Dyskinesia", "Azotemia", "Malar rash", "Jaundice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypotension?", "answers": ["Joint stiffness", "Blurred vision", "Toe walking", "Neuralgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Hypotension?", "answers": ["Lightheadedness", "Fecal incontinence", "Fibrosis", "Groin Lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Waxy flexibility", "Osler's sign", "Angina Pectoris", "Pulmonary hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Syncope", "Abscess", "Hypomania"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Stiffness", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Weight gain", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Genital sores", "Hyperpigmentation", "Headache", "Deafness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Malignant Skin Neoplasm", "Dry cough", "Candidiasis", "Torticollis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Glabellar reflex", "Chorea", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Conjunctivitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Chest pain", "Barrel chest", "Excessive daytime sleepiness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Gingival enlargement", "Dyspnea", "Waxy flexibility", "Delayed reading ability"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Hypertension", "Tophus", "Malocclusion", "Muscle atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Chronic cough", "Stunted growth", "Cullen's sign", "Chronic pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Cyanosis", "Paget's disease of the breast", "Periorbital puffiness", "Parosmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Fever", "Bleeding", "Hemiparesis", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Hypothermia", "Stupor", "Vision loss", "Chest Tightness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Ileus", "Lack of empathy", "Blister", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Dry Eye", "Nocturnal enuresis", "Bradycardia", "Bloating"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Proteinuria", "Oligomenorrhea", "Medulloblastoma", "Peripheral edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Mental illness", "Ascites", "Cullen's sign", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cardiovascular disease?", "answers": ["Bleeding diathesis", "Genital ulcer", "Restricted behavior", "Dizziness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alcoholism?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Tic", "Steatorrhea", "Trousseau sign of malignancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alcoholism?", "answers": ["Fatty liver", "Sinusitis", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca", "High Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alcoholism?", "answers": ["Hematuria", "Respiratory arrest", "Micrographia", "Muscle pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Alcoholism?", "answers": ["Spider angioma", "Lymphocytopenia", "Portal hypertension", "Bronchiectasis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Leukoplakia", "Obturator sign", "Bell's palsy", "Vision disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Esophageal varices", "Wheals", "Deafness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Disinhibition", "Neck mass", "Vasculitis", "Wandering"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Spasticity", "Dysentery", "Hyperthermia", "Sore throat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Dysesthesia", "Eosinophilia", "Erythroplakia", "Hypomania"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Angular cheilitis", "Fibrosis", "Dysphagia", "Trismus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Acalculia", "Otalgia", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Nephritic syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Sexual obsessions", "Erythroleukoplakia", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Failure to thrive", "Hutchinson's sign", "Dry Eye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral cancer?", "answers": ["Loose teeth", "Scaly skin", "Palmar erythema", "Hyperlipidemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Nausea", "Deafness", "Hypocalcaemia", "Conductive hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Intertrigo", "Peripheral neuropathy", "Swollen tonsils", "Azotemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Vertigo", "Diaphoresis", "Gastric varices", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Iritis", "Anorexia", "Red eye", "Restless legs syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Hypersomnia", "Vesicle", "Scleritis", "Oliguria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Myopathy", "Acute abdomen", "Middle back pain", "Kehr's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Pyoderma gangrenosum", "Vaginal discharge", "Chemosis", "Cirrhosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Ventricular tachycardia", "Depression", "High Fever", "Hunger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Gingivitis", "Tremor", "Difficulty Focusing", "Nocturnal enuresis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Hematochezia", "Hegar's sign", "Quadriplegia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Restricted behavior", "Pressure of speech", "Hirano body", "Enthesitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Cardiac asthma", "Spinal tumor", "Uveitis", "Sexual obsessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Rose spots", "Bone Loss", "Thyrotoxicosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Emaciation", "Heberden's node", "Flatulence", "Body ache"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Air crescent sign", "Mastodynia", "Restricted behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Agnosia", "Osler's sign", "Erythema nodosum", "Hypercholesterolemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Pancolitis", "Floater", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Delayed puberty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Palmar erythema", "Feeling of impending doom", "Decreased level of consciousness", "Anal fissure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Painless testicular lump", "Gynecomastia", "Boredom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Emaciation", "Stroke", "Infertility", "Air crescent sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Pneumatosis intestinalis", "Stuttering", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Insomnia", "Bloating", "Golden S sign", "Phlegm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Arthropathy", "Obesity", "Dysphagia", "Hypomania"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Seizure", "Flashback", "Vascular Leak", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Dizziness", "Intellectual disability", "Kehr's sign", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Hot flash", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Constipation", "Keratoconjunctivitis sicca"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Failure to thrive", "Polyphagia", "Nasal polyp", "/m/0lxt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Erythema multiforme", "Golden S sign", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Tic", "Kehr's sign", "Malaise", "Joint pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Pneumonia", "Azotemia", "Skin rash", "Immunodeficiency"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Phonophobia", "Stereotypy", "Hypoesthesia", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Bladder spasm", "Vaginitis", "Arthritis", "Atrophy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Crohn's disease?", "answers": ["Abdominal pain", "Brain damage", "Halos around lights", "Difficulty Focusing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Inverted nipple", "Vital Exhaustion", "Tachycardia", "Spider angioma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Hypercholesterolemia", "Anorexia", "Vasoconstriction", "Mental illness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy", "Left ventricular hypertrophy", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease", "Loss Of Consciousness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Stupor", "Melena", "Hypertonia", "Hepatic encephalopathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Arthropathy", "Hemiplegia", "Palpitation", "Hepatorenal syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Hepatopulmonary syndrome", "Deformity", "Red eye", "Bacterial vaginosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Wart", "Vaginal dryness", "Dysphonia", "Hypogonadism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Azotemia", "Nail clubbing", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Pneumonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Tophus", "Polyphagia", "Jaundice", "Uveitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Indigestion", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Central facial palsy", "Portal hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Pallor", "Asymptomatic", "Muscle weakness", "Muscle Spasms"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Chronic pain", "Esophageal varices", "Urinary retention", "Rose spots"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Ageusia", "Splenomegaly", "Melanocytic nevus", "Frontal release sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Vaginal bleeding", "Astasia-abasia", "Disregard for right and wrong", "Ascites"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Menorrhagia", "Runny nose", "Feeling of impending doom", "Hepatomegaly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Eructation", "Unintentional Weight Loss", "Intrusive thoughts", "Delusional misidentification syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Peripheral edema", "Dysautonomia", "Bradykinesia", "Asterixis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Bouchard's nodes", "Joint pain", "Palmar erythema", "Lethargy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Stereotypy", "Fetor hepaticus", "Penile discharge", "Mole color changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Dupuytren's contracture", "Bloating", "Palpitation", "Photopsia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Myxedema", "Pruritus", "Oliguria", "Dyspareunia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Bleeding diathesis", "Middle back pain", "Tonsillitis", "Gynecomastia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Caput medusae", "Trismus", "Back pain", "Anemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Lactose intolerance", "Postural instability", "Paranoia", "Muehrcke's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Restless legs syndrome", "Air crescent sign", "Lightheadedness"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cirrhosis?", "answers": ["Difficulty walking", "Mastodynia", "Eczema", "Terry's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Enanthem", "Seborrheic dermatitis", "Hyperactivity", "Diarrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Compulsive behavior", "Mastodynia", "Indigestion", "Ageusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Dysphagia", "Alopecia", "Leg pain", "Steatorrhea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Hirano body", "Abdominal obesity", "Hypothermia", "Nausea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Weight loss", "Conjunctivitis", "Fibrosis", "Menorrhagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Oligomenorrhea", "Risus sardonicus", "Audible pop at time of injury", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Bleeding", "Deformity", "Pretibial myxedema"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Snoring", "Major depression", "Anhedonia", "Abdominal pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Stomach cancer?", "answers": ["Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Bloating", "Bronchiectasis", "Dystonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Dysarthria", "Tree-in-bud sign", "Bronchospasm", "Synovitis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Pectus carinatum", "Malnutrition", "Groin Lump", "Intermittent claudication"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Meningism", "Uremia", "Spasmodic dysphonia", "Tachypnea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Swelling", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Sputum", "Hypertriglyceridemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Anhidrosis", "Fibrosis", "Anxiety", "Odynophagia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Chest pain", "Facial pain", "Hypercapnia", "Kaposi's sarcoma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Pain", "Asterixis", "Watery eyes", "Respiratory arrest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Phlegm", "Cerebellar ataxia", "Intertrigo", "Polyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Hyperthermia", "Depression", "Shallow breathing", "Nosebleed"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Myocardial infarction", "Pulsus paradoxus", "Irritability", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Hirano body", "Crepitus", "Maculopapular rash", "Hyperventilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Amnesia", "Hyperacusis", "Dyspnea", "Eczema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Erythroplakia", "Hypotension", "Chest Tightness", "Cardiac arrhythmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Stomatitis", "Pursed lip breathing", "Mastodynia", "Tachycardia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Mouth breathing", "Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Cardiac asthma", "Brain damage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Cervical lymphadenopathy", "Stereotypy", "Eosinophilia", "Hirano body"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Pus", "Steatorrhea", "Chorioretinitis", "Wheeze"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Tetany", "Cardiac arrest", "Excessive Crying"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Cyanosis", "Hot flash", "Hyperesthesia", "Arthropathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Hypersomnia", "Oropharyngeal dysphagia", "Spasmodic dysphonia", "Nocturnal Cough"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Skin lesion", "Thrombocytopenia", "Fatigue", "Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Short stature", "Orthopnea", "Verbosity", "Intellectual disability"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Rhonchi", "Myxedema", "Mouth ulcer", "Alopecia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Air crescent sign", "Sneeze", "Steatorrhea", "Rebound tenderness"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Asthma?", "answers": ["Cough", "Testicle pain", "Pelvic inflammatory disease", "Osteophyte"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Central facial palsy", "Swollen lymph nodes", "Atrophy", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Telangiectasia", "Sleep apnea", "Nausea", "Alopecia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Psychomotor retardation", "Hemiplegia", "Sore throat", "Lack of Concentration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Mouth ulcer", "Visual verbal agnosia", "Halos around lights", "Male infertility"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Oral candidiasis", "Audible pop at time of injury", "Lack of empathy", "Swelling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Joint pain", "Polyneuropathy", "Fever", "Myerson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Skin ulcer", "Change in bowel habits", "Chancre", "Post-nasal drip"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Enuresis", "Paresthesia", "Albuminuria", "Genital ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Blister", "Nocturnal Cough", "Watery eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Jaundice", "Pruritus", "Albuminuria", "Terry's nails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Fibrosis", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Raynaud's phenomenon", "Asymptomatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Nipple tenderness", "Leukorrhea", "Bruxism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Herpes labialis?", "answers": ["Compulsive behavior", "Fasciculation", "Hypokinesia", "Skin rash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Unintentional Weight Loss", "Sadness", "Personality or behavior changes", "Skin Discoloration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Myxedema", "Rectal tenesmus", "Vasculitis", "Somnolence"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Glossodynia", "Red eye", "Speech delay", "Edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Oral bleeding", "Diaphoresis", "Conductive hearing loss", "Pruritus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Uremia", "Vital Exhaustion", "Vision loss", "Speech delay"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Encephalopathy", "Sleep deprivation", "Post herniorraphy pain syndrome", "Hyperpigmentation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Nail clubbing", "Erythema nodosum", "Parkinsonism", "Hypertension"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Hypertonia", "Genital ulcer", "Nausea", "Melena"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Slight redness of skin in ear canal", "Monomelic amyotrophy", "Osteoporosis", "Mental confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Paresthesia", "Malaise", "Sore throat", "Apathy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Azotemia", "Hypomania", "Bouchard's nodes", "Restricted behavior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Fasciculation", "Pericarditis", "Biliary colic", "Thrombocytopenia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Obturator sign", "Hyperpigmentation", "Metabolic acidosis", "Eosinophilia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Hyperkalemia", "Vaginitis", "Difficulty walking", "Sexual dysfunction"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Sneeze", "Eczema", "Dysesthesia", "Pulmonary edema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Tonic\u2013clonic seizure", "Iritis", "Bloating", "Tertiary hyperparathyroidism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Hyperesthesia", "Hiccup", "Loose teeth", "Hypercapnia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Anger", "Hyperphosphatemia", "Hemolytic anemia", "Hypersexuality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Fatigue", "Nephritic syndrome", "Fourth heart sound", "Breast lump"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Infertility", "Loss of smell", "Xerophthalmia", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Headache", "Granuloma", "Acute bronchitis", "Neck pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Pruritus ani", "Paresthesia", "Hypocalcaemia", "Sleep disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Chronic renal failure?", "answers": ["Nasal congestion", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Cardiac arrhythmia", "Major depressive episode"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Rectal pain", "Dysuria", "Cervical cancer", "Hematemesis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Frequent urination", "Bouchard's nodes", "Type 2 diabetes", "Irritability"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Tunnel vision", "Post-void dribbling", "Rovsing's sign", "Halos around lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Urinary retention", "Vascular Leak", "Convulsion", "Ileus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Hematuria", "Anhidrosis", "Enuresis", "Abdominal mass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Facial swelling", "Hot flash", "Paranoia", "Urinary tract infection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Benign prostatic hyperplasia?", "answers": ["Feeling of impending doom", "Dysautonomia", "Candidiasis", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Hematochezia", "Hypersomnia", "Erythema", "Polyuria"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Dyschezia", "Skin ulcer", "Dizziness", "Mole color changes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Dandruff", "Anhidrosis", "Urinary incontinence", "Mouth ulcer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Pain", "Opportunistic infection", "Excessive daytime sleepiness", "Failure to thrive"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Foul smelling urine", "Ageusia", "Blumberg sign", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Scaly skin", "Glossodynia", "Autoimmune hemolytic anemia", "Wandering"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Forgetfulness", "Hyperlipidemia", "Lower motor neuron lesion", "Dysgeusia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Cervical cancer", "Halitosis", "Sleep apnea", "Bleeding"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Delirium", "Anhedonia", "Dysphagia", "Bladder spasm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Oral candidiasis?", "answers": ["Bradykinesia", "Blood in stool", "Pharyngitis", "Panic attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Bloating", "Splenomegaly", "Lactose intolerance", "Acne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Bigger mole diameter", "Intestinal pseudo-obstruction", "Erythema multiforme", "Malaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Otalgia", "Abdominal pain", "Stunted growth", "Narcissism"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Anorexia", "Alopecia", "Necrosis", "Fourth heart sound"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Poor wound healing", "Dehydration", "Facial swelling", "Wheals"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Lymphocytopenia", "Fatty liver", "Nausea", "Crepitus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Sensorineural hearing loss", "Crackles", "Hypomimia", "Vomiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Fetor hepaticus", "Watery diarrhea", "Blurred vision", "Narrow stools"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Cheyne\u2013Stokes respiration", "Bleeding", "Cotton wool spots", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Hypercapnia", "Fecal incontinence", "Auditory hallucination", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Halitosis", "Failure to thrive", "Muscle pain", "Conductive hearing loss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Cyclosporiasis?", "answers": ["Allergic bronchopulmonary aspergillosis", "Flatulence", "Substance abuse", "Gastroesophageal reflux disease"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Sinusitis", "Melena", "Restless legs syndrome", "Bronchophony"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Hyperglycemia", "Ketoacidosis", "Bruise", "Fatigue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Pica", "Monomelic amyotrophy", "Testicle pain", "Audible pop at time of injury"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Furuncle", "Hyperphosphatemia", "Tachycardia", "Hutchinson's sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Verbosity", "Cotton wool spots", "Dyspnea", "Spasmodic dysphonia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Intermittent claudication", "Pharyngitis", "Hyperthermia", "Hypercholesterolemia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Malaise", "Barrel chest", "Encephalopathy", "Hepatopulmonary syndrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Barrel chest", "Anuria", "Penile discharge", "Palpitation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Nerve injury", "Neck mass", "Air crescent sign", "Pleuritic chest pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Depression", "Thought insertion", "Vasculitis", "Granuloma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Agnosia", "Hirano body", "Lethargy", "Headache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Dysphoria", "Koilonychia", "Phyllodes tumor", "Dysosmia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Goitre", "Clouding of consciousness", "Erythema nodosum", "Emotional insecurity"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "What is a symptom of Anemia?", "answers": ["Glabellar reflex", "Delusional misidentification syndrome", "Pallor", "Arthritis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}